Thank you.
the person on he did say something bad and I told him not to say it I said don't talk about kids
I mean what can I say besides that all I can tell him is don't do that you know
on my fault like people think I can control what comes out of it you let him
did I let out did I say don't say that I think I did but whatever and you're
I'm having some delicious coconut shrimp.
It's a fucking bomb.
There you go.
But I do apologize, you said that, but.
I don't have the ability to control other people's mouths.
I don't know what I can predict what's going to come out of it.
Part of the fun of like, you know, being a human being,
we just don't know everything about everything, right?
I have no idea about any of that. I even know you had kids, so.
The second time you've accused me of saying something about them when I have it,
you're actually talking about my family, but, um,
you know,
This is only problem if I do something, right?
Go ahead be your little henchman Tony or whoever you are I'm harassing me some more. It's illegal by the way, you know, so
Everything being documented
I'll make it my life's purpose is how about make your life purpose take care of your own kids?
I mean you do but
Why would be concerned about some streamer like me?
It's really you're gonna you're gonna put all your anger and all your energy into me
I don't know kind of sounds lame
But do you do you you do you boo you do you?
28 people on chat can someone say hi
No, no one even wants to say hi or they're unblocked. I don't know. Yeah, that's what's up. I
Don't know hi. Hey, Shantae. What's up? The link is up. Help me pin the link
There's my Lincoln's Panned.
Do I eat bone broth?
I heard that's really good for you though,
like making broth boiling bones, that's pretty good.
I'd eat it.
I'm gonna see the full version of the thumbnail.
Here you go guys, you got it, you got it.
I know it didn't all fit on the thumbnail, but I got it.
Wow, you really are sick you let that man speak disparaging of an innocent kid guy cult of psyche
I will make it my goal to destroy you
Here you go
To destroy me
After Pilates you divin and bone broth I
Don't know I know this story of stone stone soup. Have you heard of the story of stone soup? It's a really good story actually
This guy has, like, a stone, and he's hungry.
So he goes to this person and they have a garden.
And he's like, oh, can I have some stuff in my garden?
I'm making some of my delicious stone soup,
and I'll share it with you.
The guy's like, stone soup?
That's nothing.
That story changed you forever, right? Yeah, they stone soup. That's that's nothing like you know
What is it and he's like a lot of magical stone and it makes the soup so delicious
And it would just be even better if I had some carrots guys like no go away
So the guy goes outside and he does a big ceremony of making this putting the stone in the the water
I'm just boiling it and the old man or whoever's in the house looks outside. He said what are you doing?
And he's like, okay. Well, you can have some of my carrots
Okay, that soup sounds to just verbally not physically at Kate
She's gonna verbally destroy me. Okay. Well, she's pretty much tried to do that the other night, too
I mean, it's like, okay, go ahead not physically. Okay. Well, I won't take it as a death threat, but
Anything happens to me. You know, there are death threats out there
You got that soup say I like you a shanty, you know that story
You're being pleasant now. So maybe I was wrong about you. So if you'd like to come on panel, I promise I'll be respectful
Yeah
Yeah, basically the stone is just it's just like the kind of like a trick
Thank you. Oh
The second you know, they got insulted verbally not physically I know I know I didn't
Yeah, some she I mean something was said and I said don't say that. I don't know how to like
do anything besides say don't say that or don't talk about kids and stuff like that.
So I said your cat's name is Nor. It's cute. Oh my god, look at Lola.
You're getting the covers? You're getting the little blankets?
Here.
That's Miss Lola.
If you want to come up, you're welcome.
Welcome up.
I know.
I mean, and it's not even, I don't know anything about it,
and I don't want to, like, talk about anybody's kid,
and so I just don't know.
I just don't know, like, what, I don't know if there's anything there.
Okay. After your transition.
Don't know. It's always a clutched your pearls moment around me, right? I
Don't know I'm so controversial
but I
Don't support like even making fun of people's kid. I don't know anything about it
Beed is bad over Sam and something. I don't even know if I know anything about Q's picture. No, I
Thought it was a picture of me. I was like, why am I like the back of like
You know an old Puerto Rican woman. I don't I don't know
That's supposed to be a Sam and I guess but I
Don't fucking know
People think I just know everything. Oh play dumb. I am dumb
You know I'm dumb right now. I'm a fucking dumb ass
You're mad at me about that I mean don't make fun of dumb people I
See dumb people. Well, we don't want to have one more ship left. These were awesome by the way
Shout out to the wonderful donator that got me fucking delicious food
Great old thing
Sweet chili sauce
Mmm
Yeah, but I'll apologize to her but I mean I apologize that he said that but
It's really for him to apologize. I don't know anything about it right now turning more into more. Oh
I like charisma
I'm gonna call charisma. Can I help you? Can I help you Riz for sure?
Um
But yum yum yum yum. That was good. Thank you so much the food. Hey Lenore
And nor nor
And nor nor I
Don't know Christians of Christians a big fake to Christine like you know, she was so nice the other night
It's always Amanda and then the next time I saw them get the fuck out of here psyche get out of here loser
Blah blah, and it's like they just say stupid shit
Like whatever do you women? Well, I didn't make the SpongeBob Amanda pants cartoon
But everyone had a laugh about that, right? I don't know
Where's the SpongeBob Amanda pants? I still have it
I do
At least she was laughing about it the other day
Have you how about this day puff
Marshmallow Amanda. Have you seen that one?
It's a good one, too.
Oh my god, who's the guy in the apartment?
She looks good. I don't know if I could have a Christine video.
Christine.
in the Christine video.
Oopsie.
Oh my gosh, sweepies here.
Hello, my brother.
I thought it was Sweet Pea.
Oh, what's up, Arthur?
How are you?
How are you, Arthur?
You hear me?
The YouTube app doesn't show all of that.
What's going on?
Is it Kate Hate Week?
I don't know, but I don't hate Kate, but with Kate.
Can you read the thumbnail?
Because I can't really.
It doesn't show all of it.
I got to put it on the screen right now.
Here's the thumbnail.
That's it.
This is the thumbnail from today.
It's a couple hours ago.
Read it out loud Arthur. Can you read it?
It's still not on stream yard. I'm waiting. All right. There you go. It's on you to YouTube
It mentioned you in a post. Wow, you were really sick. You just let the man speak disparaging on an innocent kid
Psych you will make it my goal to destroy you
Yeah, now I was there. I was listening. I wasn't there there, but I was listening while you guys were on panel
Did you hear me say I'll tell him to not say that and correct you did tell him to not to stay away from that.
You did not encourage him to continue with that.
But I also get Kate where she was already telling you hey, this guy is no good.
And then he goes ahead and then he talks about her child so.
I don't know if there's a B for history with them, you know, in the past, because she seems like total utter destruction.
Well, yeah, well, what are you going to do? What are you going to do?
Can you, is there any way that, you know, look, when I sometimes eat whether I'm right or wrong, I'll just be like, you know what, fuck it.
I've been to me. I'm so sorry that happened. I said I said I'm sorry, but I said I can't I'm not responsible
What comes out of people's mouths and I said I did tell them not to say that so
But right now like can you tell her? Hey look, honey? Like look, I'm not gonna tell her
But I already said it on the show. I said, I'm sorry. Did he said that?
At the same time, I'm not responsible for what comes out of other people's mouths.
It's not what, it's not my, I don't endorse it.
I, I'm, you know, people can say, I can't predict what's going to come out of people's
mouths, right?
It's like, you know, there's only so much I can do.
All I can say is don't say that.
I mean, that's all I can say.
Oh, don't roll your eyes at me, Amanda.
Don't roll your eyes at me.
Stop it.
Amanda, stop it.
No.
Don't laugh at me.
Don't laugh at me, Amanda.
Stop it.
Oh, Christine, Christine, you look beautiful.
Oh, look at those, look at those.
That hair.
Oh my God, I love your hair.
I love it.
I mean.
Hey, I know you deep down you do get along with psych and I know psych gets along with you
Let's just you know, let's I don't I don't want to get full out war
But it's like it's like all of a sudden and she does like four our lives about me five hour lives of talking about my family
Talking about I'm dirty talking about I don't take care of my cats because my cuz tricks ran away and stuff like that
Can I help it tricks ran away? Can I help that? You know, it's like what did I want? No, do I have?
a bodily control of him and I can just like you know call him back and it's like no cats are
independent you know and so as part of the danger of having indoor outdoor cat you know but at the
same time I think there's benefits to having the cat be able to go outdoors too and some cats want
to be single cats some cats want to be in a family you know I love tricks his brother came back
I'm like, I hear with his mom.
Wait, Trix was a dude?
Yeah, Trix is a boy.
Yeah.
Oh, why would you name him Trixie?
Well, because he's kind of feminine.
He's a little bit feminine, but I can't.
I think he was gay, or he's gay.
But you know what?
This is no offense, and this is why I think
gay couples should not adopt children.
Why not?
What do you have to say?
I think, like, you guys start to lay
teach the adopted ones that it's okay to be like that.
And deep down, when you look at the real world, not just humans, but animals.
You know, there's a male and a female and the animals practice homosexuality almost every species. I think that's that's not true
It's only like seahorses. I think no, it's not seahorse. Seahorses are can pregnant themselves
Not you're you're very confused Arthur. You need to reset your your biology textbook. No, this is this is street pee
Hey, thank you. Yeah, sweetie. Why are you pretending to be Arthur?
He's such a scumbag. I so I wanted to imitate him now
Yeah, okay
I'm actually on my way to Starbucks.
You're already in Starbucks?
Yeah, I was earlier.
Somebody asked me for my name.
I told them it was Sweet Pea, and they actually
complimented me.
Did they write about what?
They said it was a cute name.
They did.
But you know the Sweet Pea is actually a poisonous plant?
Um, but it's beautiful on the outside, so don't fuck with me.
That's what that means.
Yeah.
It was like a rose.
You know, a rose will be like, you know, so, so beautiful.
And then it's like, but it has a thorn, right?
Us women are like that.
And I mean, aren't you at the end of the day a little feminine as well?
I am.
I am done.
So aren't you like a rose?
I'm like a rose.
You're a little rosebud.
Oh, I love that. I love that little rose bud that I pulled out from the rose
Throw it on the floor and stomped on it. What? P.O.S.
What?
You see me? I'm sorry. That's just the inner beta in me talking. I'm sorry. Oh my god. Is this beta?
What do you want, my friend, I'm back.
What do you want?
I am back.
You leave my family for me run alone, Psyche.
That wasn't even your family.
That was Samans or something about Saman.
It wasn't even like something related to you.
You're asking about my family and stuff.
And I like it.
I didn't even know.
I thought it was a picture of me and a Puerto Rican woman.
That's all I know.
I don't know anything about the accused for sure.
Did you mention my people, the Puerto Ricans?
Who's you want to talk about it Christine your little bitch? Oh my god. It's Christine. Oh my god
Yeah, you keep talking about me now. You said the Puerto Ricans. What's up with that?
Well, I know you're Puerto Rican you're poor. Yeah, I'm white and Rican
You're a Rican
That's what we say half white half reekin. What is BKG? I don't know, but here's all I have to say about BKG
Wait, hold on hold on hold on you should ask chat GBT to give you a
funny or disrespectful
acronym for BKG
Barry and Kate King
No, no, no, no ask ask a GBT to give you like a very disrespectful BKG acronym with like
Yeah, let me see. Let me see. I'll go to chat to you. What are some funny?
Insulting funny insulting acronyms for BKG
Okay, okay it says okay barely known goblin
But you know, yeah budget knockoff genius basic keyboard gremlin
Oh background knowledge gone bad karma generator. Oh, that's a good one
Then there's broken knowledge generator big knucklehead girl budget kind of genius
blatantly clueless goof
King of garbage, brain cells keep gone, big-time knowledge gap,
barely keeping grounded, built kind of garbage, beyond known growth,
banana kung fu guru, bizarre kangaroo gang, burrito knowledge guild,
binary ketchup god, and basement crack in general. How are those?
Wow, I mean, I like it.
That's what she is
Like that sorry those are fun. I like I like the basic basic basic goblin whatever it said. It's a basic some basic
Nuclea dragging goblin basic. No barely known goblin barely known bitch has beta
Yeah, well, that's my cat Lenore my bk g-tab she has Lenore on it and the north saying
Yeah
You'd be to say
Who Ashanti who are you Ashanti? Are you Ashanti the singer?
Male lions reinforcing social bonds wildlife on safari. I like that WOS woes
male lions reinforcing social bonds that is true
How are you Arthur Arthur? You know, I like you a lot. You know, I don't love you. I just like you a lot
Appreciate that brother. Well, I mean, I don't want to go too far
Mass on you know, okay
Sorry, you know who is live right now, you know, I won't say his name. Oh
Is he something like this?
He was talking shit about you just now. Oh, my gosh. What a shocker
That's a shock
Yes
Yeah, I mean, okay, hold on. I'm gonna update Arthur's shoes. Let me get a picture of these real quick. Yes. Yes
I'm gonna put on your shoes on you. Okay. Yes. No boots. Please cowboy boots. Okay. I'll do cowboy boots
Let me just get the picture. Yes. Thank you
Okay, here we go
Okay, I gotta go to my website, yep, you're gonna get some brand new shoes Arthur. I hope you like these ones
Let's go, baby. Let's go
Okay, and I'm gonna put it in here. I'm gonna say an ad media
Okay
Okay, oh baby
Give it a guess coming in let's welcome our next guest
Let's welcome to the show. I'm scared. Who is it? Oh, you know, Arthur, you should be ashamed of yourself
Have you read the YouTube to us?
what
What am I not allowed to say I
Mean, I mean, are you serious? How could you sit up here and be disrespectful with somebody like psyche?
You should be disgusted with yourself. You're such a terrible human being
Like honestly, you should you should just
You should do yeah, I can't even say
No, I'm not gonna break TOS because unlike you psyche or not psyche unlike you Arthur
I've actually read the TOS. Okay, and I'm well versed in the TOS
What the fuck is going on? My name is my name is Christian. Oh my god
I'm not
I am Christine's alter ego.
Oh my God.
And you will not get away with that with breaking the TOS
as long as I am around.
OK, Arthur?
Arthur, I have them ready.
Are you ready to see the new shoes?
Yeah, you put them on YouTube.
I can't see them on.
I got them on YouTube.
OK, here you go.
Here's Arthur's new pair of shoes.
And here you go, Arthur.
I hope they're boots.
Think so. Oh, what the fuck? Yo, what is wrong with you? Wait? Yes, we're hell. No, dude
The heels. Yeah, ready heels. Oh
Some fucking Steve Madden
What are you doing? You like those? No. Oh, no, I'm so sorry
Hold on. That's gay. I'll do your boots. I'll change them to boots. Okay. I mean those boots that you were wearing in that picture
Kind of gay too though. Come on
You got boots and tight pants on like no, there's shorts
He's wearing basketball shorts. He's wearing like Nike and Nike basketball shorts swimming shorts swimming shorts
His butt looks so good in them. Seems like he'd be really easy to bend over. Yeah
I love, okay, oh my God, this is a great one.
Arthur, I think I got him.
I think I got you the right one.
Oh my God.
I'm scared, I ain't gonna lie, I'm scared.
I said change him to cowboy boots.
I mean, I don't know, I don't know, okay, oh.
Well, here's one pair that they gave me.
So, here we go.
See this one?
Okay, so here's the next pair of Arthur's shoes.
Arthur, do you wanna try on this pair of shoes?
Let me know when they're on YouTube.
They're almost up, okay, here we go.
was better
Hold on
That's another question. Why do you what why do you rock those floods?
What's up with the floods?
Dude, what the fuck is that?
No, no, no, no regardless regardless of the that picture like the original picture. Why do you rock floods though?
Flood no, what are floods? I don't know what floods are
You know when it's flooding you gotta, you know, you want your your shit to be of high
No
Oh, you're showing skin on your leg, like what are you trying to wear capris all the shorts?
Yes, I'm showing knees. Yes, you have hairy legs Arthur or they are you shave your legs?
It looks like it looks like you're wearing fucking the floods, bro
No, they're just regular swimming shorts. I mean I do wear I think they're like seven inch long shorts
I enjoy when they you don't even know what seven inches looks like
I wear seven inch long shorts. I can't do too long are there actually as long from where from your waist
It's a base to the tip of the waist. Yeah
They could be from the waist seven inches from your waist is that's like wearing a speed like a fucking like a wrestling trunks
Are you kidding? You're right. I don't know where they where they measured from
I don't know where they measured from all I know is where seven inch seven inches from your waist would literally be like wearing underwear outside
No, you know what I think is from the crotch
It has to be from that point. It's definitely not from it's definitely not from where your dick starts because it'll be way farther back
I'm not sure, but I just you know, I rocked them Nike seven inch
Your seven inches are so Arthur your seven inches. I just worry you're sticking to it. The five inches are too small
I'll write a video of you
And where's the thing that is is he's still around he's still alive
he's bald hold on I'll be right back I mean is he not bald what the fuck is that
oh this is the way you're this is see this is why Ram is so expensive now a
day is psyche you're gay
Wow, Victoria can come here. Yeah, Victoria Missouri is welcome. Why can't Victoria come here? Yeah
Yeah, I mean, I don't really care for Victoria that much, but we can listen to her scream for a minute if you want
No, she usually just screams at the chat
She has her that's her that's her fucking that's her shtick. That's what she's supposed to do. That's what that's her thing chicken wing
That's an anything without a chicken wing
Everybody's everybody's got their niche around here. You know, yeah, she's not she's beefing with salmon and she can come over here
Yeah, I want to she's been with salmon. Let me check. He's beefing with be the two now, you know, oh my god
I mean it was so much beef and there was no and that was only a matter of time before that one. Yeah
I know, I know, and isn't Vita not fighting with also her friend Crystal Ann?
Hey, hey, hey, don't you don't say anything about Crystal Ann. I
Like Crystal Ann, Crystal Ann's been on the show. She's cool. You better. I like Crystal Ann
I just said that I think they're beefing when she's beefing with Vita like Vita like it's turned against her
Crystal Ann on max all these people out
Yeah on Crystal Ann. Oh, we have a guest back
Yeah, oh god, here. Why am I supposed to care about her kid when she's calling me a pedophile bro slandering me dude
Fuck that. Let's just not talk about anybody's kid. Okay. Nobody's kid
Kids can't help who they are, okay, so
Every time this dude comes on panel he talks about kids like what the fuck that's what it's all panels about
We get the fucking thumbnail
So now the whole pan this whole panel is about kids no
It's about somebody crying bro about slandering somebody bro, and they fucking think it about them and they don't like it
Yeah, this is what the thought this is shows about i'll show you the thought i'll show you this picture
The comment that was made today. Here we go. This is the comment that was made. There we go
Dude talks to fucking miners on instagram is a weird. I don't prove it
What I could I could I could I could make a fake thing with you want me to do that and then send it to all your neighbors
I don't think he would like to talk to pedophiles, so whenever he leaves, I don't know if I'll talk to him.
Exactly, dude.
Well, I just wanted to say that, you know.
Don't slander somebody. That's the worst thing you could put on somebody, bro.
And she wants to slander me. Fuck her, dude. She don't even know me.
I don't even know that weirdo.
Yeah, that's all I asked is like if you knew her and then you mentioned something
I said don't mention kids and stuff and then now she's like mad at me not mad at you
She's mad at me. I don't understand. She wants to destroy me not you but anyway, well later. What is she gonna do shit?
I don't know. She can just get her her little turtle army. Well, the good thing about the turtle army is they're pretty slow
They're gonna do nothing though. Yeah, and
Yeah, so
Yeah, I'm like how disparaging is that what I said what I said is true like like oh my god, but it's like it's true
Yeah, she needs to go work and go worry about her family dude. Don't be fucking lying about me bro, because
Oh, he gets this about a money a week. Yeah
What's the difference talking about your parents or whatever? What's the difference, bro?
But but anyways man 15 year olds on Instagram. No, never did that
Never did that rain who is rain and how I don't know that she how did you know that she got her phone taken away from her by her father?
Never said that
It was rain. Oh, no, no, no, oh that was the kid. Oh you're talking about the one that gamble was trying to groom
That's that's why her mom took away her phone gamble only a gamble only ever knew who rain
No, no all those kid. No, I have I have proof of it, bro
That snowballs and all them they said that they were watching gamble first. That's how they found out about me
Oh, whenever you went off remember whenever you went off about how
You went off on rain about how oh, yeah, that's why your dad took your phone away
And that's why your dad this and that like how did you know all of this about her her and her family if you did she told
Gamble because she was typing in Gamble's chest saying oh, I'm scared my dad
Oh, no, no, no, I'm scared. I have a screenshot. I want me to show it. Watch I'll post it in psyche's discord right now
I'll post a screenshot in psyche's discord, dude. That's not that's not in Gamble's chat
There's a screenshot of Gamble's chat
with a kid in his chat that's a paid member you know on on youtube right you become green right if
you get a membership right there's a 12 year old little girl named snowballs a paid member
in gamble's chat dude and a screenshot of her saying oh i'm worried i'm worried my parents are
gonna take away my phone because i said that i was gonna let their parents know that a child
Shit ever. I have proof. I have proof. He is a pedophile. What pedophiles has he gone after?
What pedophiles has he caught? Who has he gone after? Who?
He is a pedophile. Why didn't he go after his own mom? His mom's a pedophile.
Why didn't he go after his own mom then? Why didn't he go after his own mom?
Why didn't he go after his own mom?
Gamble the motherfucker that started all these lies, but when he's the motherfucker, bro had a 12 year old girl
Yeah, what kind of do what kind of dude see up see how they shut down see how they talk all this shit and then shut down
Once I spit facts and gamble had a 12 year old girl. That was a member of his shit and
And and was collecting money from a 12 year old girl, but I'm gonna have proof. I literally have proof of it
I wonder if some people are trying to be silenced because they know too much truth
Like I like I really haven't had anybody like like argue against what you're saying
I want to hear like well. No, this is like this is this but no one no one's countered anything that you've said really
They don't they just say oh, I'm gonna leave. Oh, have you noticed that? Oh, I'm done
I'm not I don't talk to predators or oh either predator that you know what I mean, and then they just throw all remember that 15 year old girl
like a stupid bro and then when you get into it what no there's a 12 year old girl named snowballs
i was giving gamble money bro and was in his community bro and he would go live bro would be
in his chat talking shit about me bro and when crack rock chris died she would come in my chat
and be like oh oh it's been it's been a week his body starting to rot oh it's been three weeks his
Okay, I don't want to talk about it. Let's not even like reference anybody under 18
I don't know about it. Like let's just like keep it like keep it like coach. No, we all need to know about it
Bro, you need to be exposed, bro. Well, I mean, I'm saying like, you know, post on my discord
I you're the queue the queue army guy on the discord and I didn't delete
You said I something about I deleted the stream them a coward. No, all my streams are scenic. No, I was talking to that other dude, bro
Not you dude
Yeah, but yeah, all my streams are syndicated on rumble
Yeah, and trip and sip and so all my show it like you're anyone ever wonders like all my shows
It's another delete episodes because someone says something to go between too far and so I they're syndicated already and so
Yeah, I don't know. It's just weird. I mean it's like people are just you got you got everyone going so crazy
And I say maybe it's like a good conversation to have like
I'd rather have like a conversation than people accusing him. I've been accused of of being all these kind of things too on on
On YouTube, right? And it's like people will say things that it's like not necessarily true because when someone's saying it
I mean, it's like I need to see police
I need to see like, you know government paperwork about it in order to gamble dude when he would go live
He would just spread lies about me or go and tell people bro like snowballs
He goes he goes and oh he had all these victims and his name. He goes Daniel snowballs
Daniel Daniel's a ten-year-old little boy that gamble was talking to before even even knew about streaming or anything years ago
I don't want to like talk about any
Rating on my show so we can keep it over 18 if you don't mind the guys. This is like I just I don't want to I don't know
Individually and routine is a pretty much. Yeah, it's just insane, bro. Like
he's talking to a kid and then he said that that's my victim bro and i had nothing to do with that kid
i wasn't even around seven years ago bro like i just i i i really don't know the lore or enough
to even have a conversation about it but you know i'm really like like to let you
Defend yourself because you know it seems like the thing is like they want to take a bigger people's voice
Like they can't even say anything right and it's like well how can they defend themselves and how can they because people can say anything
About anybody right, but then they're not allowed to defend themselves. Hey, just jet. How are you?
Yeah, but I'm asking you one more time Brandon. Let's like just reference people 18 or over
I don't want to talk about you know making accusations or put a jacket on anybody
I don't know. I don't know gamble. All right, and I really I don't really know you and people think that
Oh, well, I'm like, you know in love with you. I'm trying. Oh, yeah
Yeah, and it's like they're saying. Oh, he's a predator catcher. He's never caught a predator bro. I caught predators
I've caught predators live on stream. He's never caught a predator. I know well just yet
I saw some of I saw a little bit of that footage and I saw her in the bed
And I saw her like I saw him like take off his shirt and stuff like that and then I mean it's like
And you know Alexander to tell me about that and she played a little bit about on her clip
I mean it didn't look right necessarily, but
And then they say talking about a kid. Okay, well you're calling me a predator and I'm telling you the person that fucking made these lies
He's the predator. What do you want me to do stay silent about it?
Track about how are you?
Fuck that bitch that bitch fucks dogs, bro
And and and Jen keep running your mouth, bro. I got all your info bro your husband's info everything, bro
Yeah, well, it's not making threats to anybody here, and I know it's not a threat
It's a promise keep my name out of your fucking mouth
I do want to like, you know, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, and I'm a bad person bro
I never beat a little girl in the fucking head with a rock bro
She beat a little girl way younger than her way smaller than her and she bastard head in with a fucking boulder, bro
Almost killed her shut the fuck up
Top reference thing under 18 people like I just like let's like keep up a show because it's like it's just crazy
Bro literally hit it chicken the head with a rock. Did you know that did you know?
She hit Alice in the head with a rock. It almost killed her and she's like twice the size of her, bro
Okay
Yeah, hey, what's about as in Nancy? I'm gonna mod. Did you have a what's my problem reality Nancy?
Why are you picking on reality Nancy?
Change the subject. It's not change the subject when they're talking shit about me
Then it's a subject once I start spitting facts about them, and it's all don't talk about it
And see and why are you picking on reality Nancy? What she do me? Yeah. Oh
Because she's talking shit about me just the same shit and chat's running her mouth about me, bro
And she's a fucking man
Don't think so. I don't think so. What do you mean? You don't think so. Look at that. That's not a man
That's a man using an AI bro. I've talked to reality Nancy
Privately, and she's not a man. I know I can tell the voice and stuff like that
So yeah, she's not a man. She's not a man. She's actually beautiful woman
And so I mean, I think you're mistaken, but and she's a really good friend of mine and you know
I just want to like I but I do want to like it lets you at least defend yourself
Because there's a lot of accusations been made against
Right a lot of you're not letting me though, bro
Who isn't hello?
Me or me or who's not letting you I am letting you speak. It's just always change. Oh, of course. He's talking about a kid
Yeah, cuz I got dirt on motherfuckers, bro
That's like saying the cops like when they're on court they're like, oh look they're talking about kids when they're fucking convicting somebody, bro
Oh, look the prosecutor's talking about kids
Like what if you're more moderators moderators can you just watch that can you just watch my chat for me a little bit?
Like if I can't do it many a few more moderators, okay?
Okay, there we go. Yeah, cuz that's how the world will work
That's how the world works, bro. Just cuz you're on the internet doesn't mean that you could run your mouth and talk shit about me
People need to learn bro, and they're gonna learn bro. They're gonna learn. Thank you Alex. Thank you. Yeah
Okay, well, you know, it's like is you're not gonna make many like, you know, like really prove yourself like by threatening people or or yeah
So yeah, so but do you have anything? I mean, I'm gonna let you wrap it up like cuz uh, oh, so you want me to get off
You don't have to defend myself. I want you to go ahead defend yourself. I'll give you like another 60 seconds
I will interrupt you say whatever you want to say this out 60 seconds, and then I'm all so you're giving me a few seconds
60 seconds 60 that's not a few that's 60. That's that's like that's fucked up, dude
Oh, it is well, you know what I could say just get out
It's just like you say oh defend yourself then once I started defending myself you're like no don't do that
No, no, I believe you 60 seconds right now. You have one minute. Let's say whatever you want to say. Okay?
All right, hold on look at this
What are we looking at the death the grim reaper? It's my uncle
What are you Santa Marte artful sir your warship or Santa Marte, right? Yeah
Okay, well all these people Jen keep running your mouth, bro
Just can't keep running your mouth, bro. At least I don't fuck dogs, bro. I'll be back, bro
Okay, I ran in
Wow
It was a grim rewrestling, it's actually a sense of warranty, yeah, um, who I reckon I recognize and it's you know
But anyway, I gave him a 60 seconds. He took 30
I mean, he's kind of being threatening and not like friendly. I was I just want to change the topic a little bit, right?
but um
He's threatening with wishcraft. I don't know but guys if you want if you can talk to me. I I know wishcraft too, okay
Yeah, that's no good, bro. No good
Look what just Jen said dude, too. She's a big fan of yours. She's faithful to you. She's nuts
It's never said anything about about you
Yeah, but she said in the chat. I mean
Just Jen and somebody did donate and they said for a reading for you
So whenever you'd like that reading, I'll be happy to do that reading for you
Someone donated for reading for you. So wait now hold on. Did you see what she said something about?
You know the previous caller having her info threatening family
That guy's got some serious issues, huh
I like to let people expose themselves and it's like I'm not gonna like just like oh
The reason why like I'm gonna say this and I'll let it go after this obviously
I don't want to talk about him forever, but I have to say this
He'll sit up here and he'll be like oh well everybody leaves whenever I start spitting facts and this and that
We've we've gone at it with him about this many times the proof is out there
I mean, what am I going to sit here and fucking scream at him over and over and over again
every single day?
I'd rather just not be up here and talk to that fucking weirdo, so I'll just let him
gas himself out and, like, he leaves, now I can come back, you know, fuck you.
Okay, yeah, I just wanted to wrap it up with him because I was gonna give him a chance to say it
He's making it. He kept talking about kids and stuff and which is about everybody knows it's I don't I I
Don't have to exhaust my fucking breath to let everybody everybody already knows about Brandon. Okay?
It's no go ahead and wrench just Jen. Come on. She is Jen. She's wrenched. Oh
We are inch to
Shantae, okay. Well, if I know you when I know you a little bit better
Yeah, that's I might do that for you and I want to say thank you again. I got a really nice generous
An angel sent me grocery groceries today and that was so I ate all the shrimp and they gave me some good air for
and and a white claw and
Everybody or signature a particular person and thank you to everybody that did donate in the past couple of days because yeah very very kind
Shout out to the officer dude. You know who it is who did that come on? Yeah shout out to amq
Yeah
Well, you go
Chante you didn't you don't care if you lose my wall. I asked me not to you don't the mod you just said like it
But you know, you don't care
my
Let's not talk about now, man. You're a sheet
Nick
What'd you say?
What'd you call me?
What'd you talk about with us?
Oh, excuse me, I'm so sorry.
Man, what'd you talk about?
What is?
That's my 70s shit right there.
Gary Coleman, yeah, that was different strokes.
Actually, I had a second cousin, or is my grandma's brother's?
Here we go.
Shut up.
Is my grandmother's brother's son?
And he was a gay man, and he worked for Good Times,
not the best streamer, he worked for the show Good Times.
He worked for Different Strokes,
and he worked for The Facts of Life
as a showrunner, production runner.
And then he had his own production company.
He was actually found electrocuted in his pool with his lover
probably like in 2020, like several years ago.
That was pretty crazy.
Like, yeah.
That's what it gets for being gay.
Oh, please shut up.
Shut up, Q. I'm gonna lick your asshole for that.
By the way good times do you name is DUI times by the way just say oh my gosh well good times
Yeah, he did get a DUI, but we know we wish him the best and his recovery or whatever he wants to do with it
But are we
He is going to drink himself if if good times gets over I will literally like it
I will that'll be the biggest miracle. I'll believe in God again
Well, you know, he came on the show drunk as a skunk the other day and he's not sober ish
He's never gonna stop drinking and the problem is is that he's gone so far down that rabbit hole
He can't just stop drinking one day like me. I could I could stop drinking tomorrow
And I won't have withdrawals there won't be any like physical effects like it'll just be like a mental thing like a craving
If that dude stops drinking tomorrow, he could literally die
Yeah, he was really drunk the other day. He was like, oh, he can't just stop drinking. Yeah. Thank you, Alexander McQueen
Thank you for doing those good. This is good moderator things. I like last week. I fucking the last week is like five days
I think you're there's like five days. I didn't drink in a row like
No beer, nothing at all like fucking if the good times did that he would die
He'd be in a hospital. Yeah, he might be shaking shaking on the street
I mean, I wouldn't move three days without drinking these other coffee was by the guy
You can't drink every you can't drink every single day and you have to stay away from hard liquor. You like
Um, that's like that that's the keys to it if you want to be a fucking alcoholic and you want to fucking like how you want to
Enjoy alcohol stay away from hard liquor. Don't drink every day. Yeah, I mean I drink like maybe five
five days a week, but also I just drink like, you know, a couple hard limonades or a couple like white claws or whatever and
I mean, yeah, no obviously no drinking is good for you
But it's better to drink fucking beers and seltzers and twisted teas than it is to drink hard liquor
Yeah, because I was drinking like I got a bottle of orange juice and a bottle of like vodka last year
And I would drink the whole bottle of vodka with the orange juice and stuff and I would wake up kind of sick and stuff
So core diversion. Yeah, let's I do wish him the best good times. He's a good guy actually. He's like I like him
It wasn't any kind of like good to you to cue. Um, like, you know, I think he was looking out for you at one point
right
What?
Was it good times ever looking up for you at one point?
Or is he like your streamer father or something?
I heard something like that.
No?
No.
OK.
The whole reason I started streaming
is because that fucking fruitcake
kept kicking everybody off panel,
so we all started our own channels.
Well, then he inspired people.
That's a good thing, right?
He inspired people.
No, that's not what the if.
You don't know the definition of inspiration then.
Well, how do you inspire? How do I inspire you Q? How do I what's how do you okay?
I'm gonna okay
So I'm gonna inspire you by smacking you in the fucking face. You'll you'll feel inspired by that
I'd like being slapped around. Yeah. No, I mean seriously if I assault you in real life
Only if you SA me to
See, that's why I don't that's can't have a serious conversation with you, dude. You're being serious
Yeah, I'm talking about some serious shit. We're talking. We're having a serious conversation and then you want to go with
Smack me daddy smack me daddy. That's all you want. That's all you fucking thinking you're my
I'll be picking your fucking your monkey
I like it. I like nigger. Oh cute more time. You're out of here
You scream that fucking word 30 times on your panel yesterday, but now I say it one time and it's a problem
I am the boss here. I'm allowed to oh, yeah, you're the fuck. Hey, you're a nigger nigger nigger
He said vinegar vinegar vinegar. I heard I just you want to hear Jim say vinegar
Hello sup nigger
He says stuff vinegar. I don't know. I don't know. But what's up on Dragon Ball you're there?
I'm doing very well. I hope everyone is enjoying their Friday. You know how it goes.
I'm so sorry on Dragon Ball. I didn't know you were there. I mean you were so quiet. I thought
it was cool too. He wants to like skew if you say it again you're gonna get unmodded okay?
Okay, my bad. Okay. Don't say it. Nigger.
Was it a horrible thing that I did to you or was it a chance for you to learn?
That that's a tough question to ask because you know, there are horrible people I hear who will do horrible things
To susceptible people
But it is what you do with that education like hey
Stop being a susceptible person in one way shape or another whether it's
Get bigger faster stronger or carry a piece or
Something like that or you know
Learn how to learn how learn how to talk to people. It's like you don't have to be
So gullible and so susceptible and so fragile for the rest of your life. You don't have to
and
What somebody may have done to you it could have been very very fucking boring. Can you shut up, please?
Oh, come on boys of reason. Come on. I like it. I like a track. He's been boring. I've been born
Nobody's here to nobody's here to be preached at by your ugly ass. Just hey, hey
Attractive man. He's an attractive man. I've seen him
I know Q's a little bit reckless. Hey, make a drag. Well, Q's not a bad guy. He's not a bad guy
I like him even though he like threatens to
He's okay, yeah, he's on my panel before he knows who the fuck I am
Yeah
Here are you gonna be doing another panel soon or?
My channel just got banned. I don't give a fuck. You have a new channel. You're new. What's your new channel called?
So everyone knows and you can subscribe
It's called at at they banned my og account
Yeah, so that's cues new channel and they ban my og account and put it on the put it on the better
Put put it on the other fucking layout, and they'll see it. Okay, hold on
Three-way layout there you go
Yeah, but in track goals a good guy. He's a he's actually a really good guy and like, you know, I do appreciate people
Yeah, but I don't need to sit here and hear his fucking shit. I really don't care
Yeah, and try to read him on trackable. I'm gonna drop the link right now
Can you read him on trackable?
Yeah, I hear
Like read no read him like tell him tell him everything about what he's doing they tell him that he's being an immature
Can you do that?
I can't tell him what you want me to tell him.
Okay, tell him what you want to tell him.
Whatever you want to say to him, tell him.
Drop the link, Psyche.
I'm dropping the link right now. Here you go.
I'm going to pin it, too.
And there, Axe dropped it for you, Q, in the chat, okay?
So thank you, Axe again.
It's not for me, it's for Alex.
No, that's for...
No, Axe dropped it for you.
He said he posted your channel name.
No, I'm saying drop the link for you the stream yard for Alex McQueen. I got you. I got you. It's chopped. It's chopped
It's chopped his pinned. It's there. Who wants to come up fucking motherfucker?
Why why didn't what so he got banned first was a nudity and that's not hard on YouTube like the AI is like going through old
Streams and like, you know, if there's like a yes
Yeah, nobody it wasn't that it wasn't like people fucking like mass reported it
It literally said in the email that like we have detected like YouTube has detected content and we use a mixture of AI and human shit to fucking
Review the content this and that I appealed it
Two hours later, they came back to me and said that it wasn't wasn't gonna get my channel back
Like I fuck it. I mean, it doesn't really matter that much. Yeah, I mean it's hard on YouTube
But it's so you can start another YouTube channel
it's like you know and
You know you can be monetized via both of my thumbs were most of the people that were stuck to me or like shit from like a long time ago like
People that don't even watch anymore, you know, so it's not really that big of a deal
And also, I don't I don't I don't use my YouTube monetization like I don't even have my super chats activated like
So it's not and I'm not attached to that channel. It's not that big of a deal
I do think it is a big deal because that was your
Venue to vent
It's your own terms. No, but I like I already have another channel though. It's not it's what I'm saying is that it's not that channel that matters
it's
It's not it's not that channel the only thing that really matters on that channel is like oh, yeah
I had like almost
3000 subscribers, but that doesn't really matter because
I don't really have like an audience. You know what I mean? Because I only stream like once every fucking three weeks
So it's not that it's not that big of a fucking deal. You know I'm saying like it's not like I'm
If I was surviving off my YouTube channel like that. Yeah, it would probably suck
That's what sucks is that you know
You will create another and create another and create another to have a venue to vent
But then you'll go on to somebody else's channel and violate their rules and I honestly
Possibly ruined their opportunity to have I just don't care about like this doesn't matter to me like like
It's not that like it's not that it's not a thing to me like for me to lose my channel doesn't matter
I already got another channel. I got 200 subs like eventually. I'll have a thousand subs again
Then 2,000 subs like if I if I keep trying you know what I mean? It's not that big of a deal
But you don't realize or you it's not that you don't realize it's that you don't even care
Listen, I don't need to hear your shit you motherfucker
Well, I don't need to hear your shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't think you understand
I don't need your fucking opinions and I don't think
Nobody cares about your opinions you fucking want to be fucking faggot. Hey, this isn't this isn't an opinion
This is real you have to say pusty. I don't care
You aren't in your house if you were to fucking start a rock band. It would be called fucking tears for bearded queers
That's totally fine. And it would probably rock out and sell out and
Be selling out stadiums, bro
Here's the kids about to run away cuz I
That's sad. Well, at least I respect people shit man like that's sad, dude
No, it's awkward. I'm really fast fast in the truck. Okay, dude
You don't know how it works, bro. Oh, I don't I've only got my channel back
But that's not even a point bro. It's just like so disrespectful bro. At least I have respect for people, you know
well, you know, I was listening for a bit of you too and
You know somebody else's place
Unless invited isn't a place to hash your shit out. It really is it like I know
Do do it at your own place. He's not like he was saying the n-word in some of my panel
No
Whatever bro, and then I'm explaining they want to know they're saying oh what about that person then I explain who that person is
And then it's a cold on puffs. Don't say that
Well, they're asking. Oh, what about this person? What about that friend? And then I explain exactly who that person is, bro
But then oh, then it's bad then it's bad because it's not, you know, like
Because because this isn't sure home
That's what I'm saying is
If if somebody says
It's not your home either then don't worry about it
Yeah, but who am I to teach anybody about etiquette?
Yeah, I'm not doing anything that's gonna get his shit taken down
They can see and that's another thing you did when something's deleted they could still see it, bro
Really, I've been able to delete like over a hundred poor moms and that's never been an issue
So I don't think it's really an issue unless it's like it's allowed there. Yeah, I
Got banned for shit that was already on
And it's like way later it comes on later
Well, I don't know I was anybody talk, you know, it's like unless he what if it was my mother's house
He broke into and it's here to have to death. Well, I know he's didn't just spend time
No, I didn't I didn't I didn't go to jail and I didn't break in anybody's house
No, I wasn't arrested. No, no, I was taken to the hospital bro because somebody drugged me bro
And that's what they said at the hospital, bro.
They said that I was drunk, bro, because they said,
well, they said, they said,
you can't remember anything for the past 14 hours.
They said that's not alcohol.
They said that's, they said that's some sort of substance.
They said,
Right, so you got Rufi?
No, GHB, because Rufi makes you pass out.
GHB makes you just lose inhibition.
You don't, and you won't remember anything,
but you're still awake.
Well, there's no cookie cutter for people's reactions to drug. No, they they that's how they pretty much act dude
Rufi will knock you out make you unconscious
GHB you'll still you'll still be awake dude
That's why they use it as a party drug too
Right
When was the last time you took GHB?
Probably wouldn't that be drug
I drank three beers. I drank three beers. They mouth like less than I drink like normally like every night, bro
Like just to chill dude and fucking yeah, remember anything for 14 hours, bro. Welcome in the hospital, dude
Yeah, I did GHB like so I had some man grinder that came here. He left a bile of GHB
And I did it like three nights in a row on my stream
Eventually the police came because they got passed out and they thought I was dead and so but uh, damn dude
Yeah, I mean that happened
Hey, there's Lola.
You know how peaceful the cat is?
She doesn't care about any of this bullshit.
She just is like sleeping peacefully, you know?
So a guy named Empathy exposed you?
Who's Empathy?
Who knows Empathy?
Expose me for what?
What did he expose me for?
I don't know.
What did he say?
Exactly.
That's all they say.
He exposed me.
Exposed me for what?
Cute oh that's clumsy look that's clumsy bro. This dude just makes shit up dude
This is the dude that you should bet that you should be banned for slander, bro. Thank you
It's like you this is this is just this is terrible
Brandon come back later. Okay. I'll talk to you later. Okay. Have a good night. Okay, so
anyway
Perfect
That dude's a fucking weirdo, bro.
Every time he comes up here,
has he, wait, let me just say this.
Has he ever come up here and like chilled
and hung out and like been chilled now?
He's always talking about kids
and like always talking about some crazy shit all the time.
He's a fucking weirdo and he's a predator.
Q, do you know Jess Jen?
Yeah, I love Jess Jen.
Me and Jess Jen are very familiar with each other.
Okay, good.
Yeah, I let him have it. I'm not gonna shit for another couple minutes
I but as I said, I want to like go away from this topic and stuff and
Yeah, so okay, so here we go. Hi Lola. He's Lola's pops. Yeah, my account got banned for no fuck. Well
so it's become I
Thinking back on it and it's also people have brought attention to me. There was a couple times where
people came up on my panel and they like
Pornbomb me and they flashed it right and I didn't get banned in that second
Then you know, I kept the stream going for an hour two hours
End of the stream didn't really think about it and I think that's where I got banned for that
You know like the YouTube AI went through my video and found the fucking the pornbomb shit
I didn't get banned for it in that moment
But yeah, they got me
So it was a good run fucking I made it I made it what like
Uh, five years with one channel, shit.
I mean, that's solid.
Especially in this community, it's back.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know and it's like, you know, everyone's gonna like masterport mass flag and stuff
It's still YouTube doesn't know the difference between like, you know, smear. I had no strikes either
Like I had no previous strikes on my channel
My channel was clean as of yesterday as of two days ago
You know, it's fucked up is that beta had seen like I did it
I published a short that had a porn bomb in it and she saw it and she didn't say anything about it
And then my channel got taken down for that. I got basically got it back, but well be the looks like a fucking a witch
They will agree. I agree. Yeah
There's also a tactic, you know tactics, right? I don't want to hear about your tactics, motherfucker
He was in the army. Let him talk
Fucking e crayons, too
As as far as these YouTube streets go and these channels go and stuff like that
If the host wants to show themselves
They could be full screen the entire time. It sounds like you're putting on a fake voice
No, this is my voice
But you know
Show nobody else don't show their avatars. Don't don't show nothing either show the host avatar or
Show the host if they want to show themselves
You can still have these same personalities on you could still have these same conversations, but nobody can buy a lead
You understand what I'm saying I
Might understand but I still don't care
Well, Q a few you have you did your 50 50 subscribers yet? Oh
I already had a backup channel. I have 200 now
Okay, that's good. So you can thank you. No, I already had a backup channel before this happened
I know and people that's the channel that I have that's posted up there the at at they banned my og account
That's the backup channel. Okay. Oh, we got it
Yeah, that's intracable. That's how intracable talks. He talks like a gangster
Like a retard. I'm intracable. I'm intracable. Hey, I'm intracable
I'll make fun of him. Come on. I
Be doing nice voice
I'm okay with it. Okay. He's okay with it. Well, he has a good sense of humor. Call me you call me Johnny boy
No, I'll call you Jonathan. I like when you well, I'm not Jonathan
It's just j o h n but I love when you call me my first name. So your birth certificate doesn't say John
It's just John. It's j o h n. Yes Jonathan is j o n a t h a n as I'm an h. That's why you're gay
No wonder cuz I'm an h in my name
No, cuz you because your name's just John not Jonathan. That's gay
Okay, well, do you know John the Baptist you heard of that person?
I'm rooming Catholic. Okay, so he's gay. We're going down the Baptist's gay
Jesus Christ don't take the Lord's name
Saying Jesus Christ isn't the Lord's name in vain. Okay, Lord's name in vain is like saying like fucking Christ
Just saying Jesus Christ is not the Lord's name in vain
Well, okay, I've ever seen the word the movie the movie priest
Have you ever seen the movie good fuck yourself?
starring Johnny Depp
No, I've never seen that who's in it Johnny Depp and who else? Hey, no the movie
I've ever seen 12 years a slave. No, but here's what the movie priest is about. There's a priest. Have you ever seen fucking?
Okay, I'm trying to I'm trying to talk right now cute. Okay as I'm sorry
It's a movie called priests is by the priest and he's gay and then he like goes out
He puts on a leather jacket goes to the gay bar and stuff and meets them meets a guy for random sex and stuff
But then he gets arrested one night
We're getting caught in the guy's car and stuff. Okay, and then
Nobody wants to take the communion from him anymore because he's gay, but this one girl
That this one like a little girl can't even got the communion from it. I don't know how much it's a really good movie queue
I mean, it's a good. It's a Catholic movie. It's a British movie. I think it was in the 90s
Once he priests
I'm going to hell for you eggs. I don't get pags. I don't get pags. I get fucked or I fuck
What is that I hear I hear a noise that noise what was that noise I heard I heard like I
Think that was fucking trackable, dude
It's when someone just made a really gay voice. Who is that?
That was you on trackable, me like, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Yeah, that was on trackable.
That wasn't him. It didn't sound like him.
On trackable, did you know how to make that sound?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
On trackable.
Hey, I did my best.
Okay, it's okay. Yeah, look at Lola. Oh Lola. Does you care about any of this Brandon Q shit or any of this is garbage?
Here's how much he cares which is when this falls to my leg
You want to see how much fucking? Oh?
Well, that's my ugly face
Sorry, not ugly. You're cute. Yeah, where's my here? There you go. That's how much Luna cares
We don't care about that, but Lola look there's Luna. There's Luna. Do you see Luna?
Don't give a fuck
Yeah
Why did I ever center my fucking camera on the goddamn cat? It's like impossible
I don't like this camera. I don't really don't but you have maybe the other one works better
You ever you key ever do you mean features that you love your cats your cats love you and
Maybe this one works better
This one
Hi babies
Lola look there's another cat look at that cat you see the cat. Oh she opened her eyes for some babies
She took a look took a look. Well, thank you to keep her showing you the cat. Oh
I ate all the shrimp by the way. It was really good. It was this coconut shrimp. I don't know where ginger is ginger is probably
Downstairs being a fucking orange and weird
That's what I just ate. It was really good
Shout out to the Donator
Send me some groceries for the week, and I appreciate you so much. I love you
Don't donate me some money. What the fuck?
Well, I mean, it's like, you know, you can drop your cash up. I don't care, you know, put it under your name
I think allow that
No, we all you guys we all need some help sometimes, you know
It's like it's like no one's gonna be able to pay the rent with the donations, but maybe they're need a little patience
Yeah
Alfredo you love shrimp little
Patience was delicious. It was it's good coconut shrimp. I also got some like
some chicken patties, I got some bananas, I got some, I got an apple, white claw.
I got all I got is a while I went to the store earlier, I bought a fucking
about 12 pack of beer about some burgers and some cheese and I got some bread.
All the shrimps we love. Yeah, OK.
I'm feeling the mood to play my commercially commercially good. No, don't do it to me, please
Yeah, but cute if you look closely, it's Zaya's face in one of the no, please
Space and one of the Mexican guys on a panel. It's gonna this big five minutes long. It's not it's 30 seconds
It's literally 30 seconds. Well, you already saw it. Okay. Okay. Okay. Where is it? Okay, so it's
Hey, you just think that said have a little patience and now you're worried about 30 seconds
Yeah, you never heard that song. It's a guns and roses song
It's literally 30 seconds long and here's like I'll play real quick. There's 30 seconds long
And it's a commercial for me. And so I want you guys if you if you if you are if you qualify
Just let me know here it is right here
Let's see here we go
Here we go
Latino, living in California, have a criminal history under the age of 30, familiar with
Santa Muerte, into live streaming, enjoy distributing illegal substances.
If so, you might be perfect for Psyche's Boys Club.
That was it. That was it actually kind of agree with her
You are you're gonna join my boys club
No, I think that you know, you're just I think people need to watch out for you all along the West Coast
Well, maybe they do especially your butthole
Okay, I mean you laugh, okay
No, your face your face changed so quick when I said that
Okay, well that was that I didn't know it's hilarious. I know it's okay. You don't only look like fucking
What's his name you look like what's that one serial killer's name every Dahmer?
No, not Jeffrey Dahmer the other one. I don't mean Gacy. Hold on. No
I don't know
manson now somebody in the chat worst person a person would know you like that one do you like that I look like danger
a Bundy had a Bundy Bundy
Yeah, you look like Ted Bundy Charles Manson. Definitely not definitely not beating the allegations. I have a Charles
You definitely look more like a Manson
No, no
I don't let me see. I want well
You need to look at it untrackable.
I don't know when the last time you looked at a picture of fucking Ted Bundy was,
but him and psyche are like strikingly similar.
It's not even like, especially in the eye area, you know, like the stare area.
Yeah, he could definitely let his hair down and be a Manson.
Please call me. Please call me.
Something like the oh, I do have this right here. Oh, oh, oh cute. I don't look like I don't look like
Charles Manson Q. I don't look like him. No, look at this real quick. No, not at all. I'm gonna show you real quick
Got it, okay
Here one more friend of ours is saying that needed be didn't I tried to like church you traffic her
Chose a house of random
Tied up the family at gunpoint. Do you understand that that's inside wait wait wait wait wait are you serious right now?
Are you kidding?
You need some serious
of members of a so-called religious cult where the leader they called Jesus has had three of its
followers arrested call themselves the family they came and went and the number of years in that
was there they were a pseudo religious cult what do you want to call me a murderer for i've never
killed anyone i don't need to kill anyone i take it i haven't here
Not that Persian spell, but on me.
Remorse for what? You people have done everything in the world to me.
Doesn't that keep me alive?
We get it, we get it, we get it.
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to.
Because that's what you've done to me.
You know, if I wanted to kill somebody,
I'd take this book and beat you to death with it,
and I wouldn't feel a thing.
It'd be just like walking to the drugstore.
Do you feel blame? Are you mad?
Do you feel like Bruce Bob's rep vanish?
Got friends?
Yeah, checkmate checkmate. Yeah, Mike drop. Thanks fucking God. Please stop
What you're in that big you use that you're one of the cops that arrested me. What are you?
Are you over the FBI? What's going on here?
Are you in that clip? I'm trying to find I'm trying to find my ginger
Okay
Well
I think if I put a little brown wig, I can pass me a spitting image
Abraham Lincoln hey guys
Ginger I know Luna. I know where you are you were sleeping next to me, but where is ginger?
We have to find a ginger it is time for you to eat your chicken
Ginger and Marianne, hey.
What is that little orange beach?
Hugh, are you more of a ginger or Marianne person?
I don't know what Marianne means.
Well, it's a bit like the Gilgit's Island women.
She was like the-
I don't know what Gilgit,
I never watched Gilgit's Island.
You never saw Gilgit?
Okay, I'll show you the pictures, okay?
Ginger and Marianne.
Ginger!
I know which one you're more attracted to.
Where are you, babies?
Don't I don't I don't see how you could be trapped on and not when the key
You don't see how I could be well. Here's ginger. Here's ginger and Marianne. I want you to guys. Tell me
Cute tell me which one you prefer, okay?
I've ginger and Marianne. Okay, so my downloads. Okay perfect. Okay, so who do you prefer ginger?
All right back guys, but who do you prefer Q ginger or
Where is it?
Let me show up. Oh shit. Okay. Hi babies. Give me a minute. Okay save image
Okay, it's there. It should be there. Don't throw your babies
Should be in there. Okay. Oh
Look at that fucking raccoon tail dude, holy shit, how it's real as fucking real as hell
It's like because um spunky got it me that had to oh here it is. Who do you prefer Q who out of these two?
Um, right on the right, Mary, answer your marriage.
I still love my ginger.
I say yes and yes.
I mean they're both good. They're both attractive
But if you're gonna ask me like which one I'm more attracted to definitely the one they're right
Especially because like I don't I'm not a big fan of fucking bangs dude bangs are weird
If you're not a fucking Chinese bitch, you better not be rocking banks
I'm just saying you you trapped on a desert island for your fucking opinion
What did he just say?
That's just Joe Shipley?
I don't think it's Joe.
Wait, which one?
There you go.
Oh, the ginger looks like Joe Shipley.
Let me see again.
The ginger looks like Joe Shipley?
A little bit. Joe Kiddly.
Oh, no.
Don't even, don't do that.
Okay, I'm sorry.
This is the, oh, like, there's only one ginger
that really matters around here.
Oh.
Yes.
At the time at 5 30. Okay. I should have a good night. I think I'm gonna have a good night
You don't like orange anything. I'm gonna probably get another couple. I already finished my white claws
I had three looks so fat because of his long hair. I promise he's not that bad
He's like, why'd you name me after a girl? It's okay. I only feed them twice a day
I feed them in the morning in the night time
You do? Yeah, I feed them, I feed my cats twice a day.
Well, they actually have, they have dry food available
and then I give them a couple cans of,
or a couple cans each of cat.
Sometimes I'll give them like,
like I'll give them like snacks.
They have treats right here too, like these little.
Nice.
Good. Oh, they love those.
They love that they, they like it.
Here, let's see if, let's, I'll open one right now.
Let's see if they'll.
We'll look it up.
Let's see if I'll fuck up with them.
Yeah, we got I think we got we got three flavors in here. We got fucking
Chicken recipe tuna which and
Salmon salmon, okay yum come here babies. Oh, oh my gosh look at these little fuckers they run over
They were laying together, but then Luna decided to be a dickhead, come here.
Come here.
Redheads love fish.
Oh, look at her.
Or is that her?
I'm sorry.
The black one is a girl, Luna.
And the orange one is a boy.
Gotcha.
Let's see if...
See if they enjoy, we'll try salmon.
We'll try the salmon recipe first.
Is it a salmon?
Is it taste like that YouTube host?
Yeah, it probably doesn't taste like
fucking unshoured Puerto Ricans.
Oh my God, oh my God.
You know, you know, you know.
Come here babies, come here.
I know beat me to came in today and was like, oh my god
How would you feel to start mentioning my dad and stuff like that and I didn't do it
It was just it was it it was there some cartoon image of like oh wait, I think they I think it's probably better off
Yeah, oh, they're gonna look it up. Oh, they love it. Oh, hey, stop it. Stop it. You go go that way because
Leave your sister alone share share
Yeah, ginger is a ginger is a real fat ass like seriously ginger is such a fat
Ginger will try to bully Luna out of her food constantly
And we have I'm sorry. I'm just trying to squeeze the rest of it in there. It's just a treat
You'll get fed later on it's just a treat
Don't worry
Q Q Q. Can you have the bread in or no?
I just don't talk to PDF so he can come up here and he can cry all he wants. I'm just not gonna converse with him
Okay, just just you just don't remember
Hey, man, just want to let you know bro. I hate to do this, but if I'm gonna be banded
Okay, well, you know, I mean come on like why do we want people like
He's kicked off the show
Bye sorry, I'm sorry
And people say I'm a scumbag right like I'm the worst of the worst these people come up here and fuck with me
Yeah, I mean I don't even need to use the lights we got natural light
Sorry not sorry
I mean, finally, I mean, you brought me more trouble
than you brought me.
I try to be like a libertarian kind of thing,
like let everyone talk and like everyone,
but if you're gonna be a dick to me, I don't care.
Go bitch about in my discord.
See if anybody cares, nobody is even there.
Pay attention to it, so go bitch in my discord.
Brandon.
You know, Brandon means-
They eat so goddamn fast.
They got some of these, I give these to them
for like snacks, these little like cans of food.
And then they got the
Just let me y'all mix. They're still they're still on the kitten food because they're still technically kittens. I
Think they're still I think they're kittens up until like one year or something like that
But yeah, they're still technically kittens so we get them the fucking kitten food. Yep
They have full grown about a year takes about a year before I stretch for a year a little last
And ginger is pretty much a full-grown cat at this point
Yeah, let's put these things
Yeah, I'm not gonna be bullied bullied by by people on the panel or by people in the chat unless it's you
He can bully me because I'm I'm I turn on by that, but otherwise no you can't
Okay, you're gonna go up and say hello if he comes back up. You never met him
He asked me McQueen. Well, if he finds another alt he can come back up and McQueen can have deal them between come up anyway
Dr. McQueen, the Santa Rita boy never remember Queen.
Am I afraid of Santa more today, by the way?
I mean, no hardly anybody even knows what the fuck Santa Muerte is.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, basically she's a, she's a goddess.
I mean, I'm in good terms with the goddess and the goddess has a billion different forms.
And that's one, that's one of them.
And it's maybe death and stuff like that.
But I'm cool with Santa Muerte. I'm cool with every goddess, you know.
I'm going to stick my dick up Alexander Mayer's ass.
Well, let's not say that Q.
Like, why would you say something like that?
Why not? Who cares?
Why why are you coming out? You can just say whatever you want nobody who gives a fuck right now
Why would you say but why but why are you fighting with her tonight? Like you fought backstage?
Yeah, because you don't realize I mean years ago before you ever even came around she's been fucking making websites about me
Yeah, she's about my family and my parents
Okay, okay, she like does she make a website or was she just reserved the dope name name?
She made a website
I don't she doesn't keep up with it anymore though. She doesn't keep up with the domain anymore
She doesn't pay for it anymore. Well, then it's gone
She lost the domain and so it's like I don't care. I don't care
What am I supposed to suck her dick nowadays because of that? What do you mean?
Hey, what's up, buddy? Yeah, what up Q ski?
Untrackable paint that garage man. Don't get me started Ronys
Oh
Where's fucking santeria boy let him back up come on. I don't have time I gotta be
Honoring the chat. He started threatening me. So I banned him from the chat
So he has to figure out another way to come up here
If you want to let him go, let's see what he has to say with the stupid shit. Yeah, he's banned
So what's wrong? See I don't like this here. Say she say shit. He did this. Oh, he says I'm lying
Like
You know, so it's all bullshit, man. You can't keep bouncing people around
That's it is corny and that's why courts of law exists like you got a show
Now you're taking their word over his and who the fuck you don't even know was really right
So, yeah, what do we do with that?
No, what these fucking goofballs get in your head
No
Bro, but you know what he threw me off with the stupid statue of a Skeletor from he man. What the fuck was that bullshit?
He's built a dumb shit this guy shows fucking Skeletor like yeah, you guys better be careful
He meant the movies coming out the summer 2026 I saw the trailer it looks fucking corny as fuck, but
You know looks good bro. There's a movie coming out Wiley Coyote versus Acme
He's gonna he's gonna sue the shit out of him for although, you know fucked up shit
They send them cuz he can't catch the roadrunner if you haven't seen
Fucking act normal, but you're gonna be fucking two homeless cats. You better stop seriously
No, we're gonna put him outside. What are they doing?
Who's that ginger their name?
Fighting
So we got ship Lee and Luna
Yeah, we got fuckface and fuckface over here fighting with each other. Hey, kids. Go. How are you?
They're perfectly well fed and they have a nice place to shit and they still want to fight for some reason
Well, they're in siblings, you know the siblings
Yeah, yeah, ginger is a foot ginger is an asshole. Are they real siblings or are they just yeah, they're real siblings. Okay
That's why they're gonna fight. They're gonna fight. They're not gonna pick on
From the same litter because one's orange and white and one's orange black and white
So that's like who has brothers here any of you have brothers where you close like I know Ronnie you have brothers some brothers
Brothers and two sisters, so there's seven
They used to pick on you when you were younger
Okay, they're like they're 10 years older. So my brother first of all my brother Derek. Okay. Oh, yeah, okay
He used to throw him everything air
And I was a little so high and he I was screaming and stuff like that
But then it's like then he went into high school and then he would fight with his girlfriend
I think her name was Marie and I was and then he had his doorknob taken off
He was seen out of the house. I think in the door on one night. He's having sex with his girlfriend
And I mean, this is crazy. I should know I should not have seen these things, you know
I was there's way she are fuck their girl before psyche
Yeah, I had a girlfriend, but she was like, oh don't even say it. I don't even know
Do you fell pussy before? Yeah
Come on
No, I went
Sloppy like I don't have a water one palm one palm stay inside how many poems how many poems I
Pumped one time just like I say I did it one time what the fuck
I had my hand in there it like squirted like Niagara Falls. I had to throw it my couch
And I told the story Jesus Christ
Yeah, so one pump and then you figured the bitch and she fucking Niagara Falls now
I don't know if that's considered sex bro. You gotta fuck some pussy for like an hour. That's
Just saying like how do you not have fun on the water slide?
I don't know what it's like his mentality is, but like there's nothing better than
To me like one of the best joys in life is being intimate with a woman
That's like that's not one if it was number one. I would have killed myself a long time. Exactly. That's all that matters
We're in life. Like, you know, you know, you never been in that. I mean you're
Create and fuck women
like a skew so and look good for them and we work out and
it's best for women
guys don't buy fucking for always because they want to impress
their fucking boy it's because they want hey hey listen hey hey
fucking gorillas don't kill each other for no reason
they fight over women same with the lions
They would lions fight over fucking families another line. Okay. Come on. Take the pride and she gets deep
It's nature. Yes
Lie cheating still why pussy?
Where any girl that's another thing yeah, that's why you got to be careful the girl you get with because that bitch can manipulate you into how and
ruin your life
If you get in your head
Oh, well, that's the story of Dante's infernal
He didn't do it because he wanted to he was trying to find the love of his life
So he crawled I bet you your fucking asshole is so wide open and whistles when you cough
Yeah
it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it
Straight pipe Chevrolet. What the hell was the Chevrolet?
I would love it if you did it, but I would love to see it.
Is that Buick? Is that Buick Chevrolet? What the hell was the Chevrolet?
Oh no, that's Psyche. Not you.
Roni guys, you know
I'm gonna come to Redondo Beach, and I'm gonna break into your house and say your fucking head off
No, we're gonna go there and when it become his security even in on trackable
He should have us wait maybe maybe I should leave him. Maybe I should enslave him
Hey
You know that other guy did someone tease them like that like I'm gonna come there and you can suck my cock every night
And I have money who was that freak?
You know
Loose asshole. No, no who fought the midget on live. You're our boy
He fought a member and he got fucked up on Twitch or some shit take I can't believe I don't remember his name
I'm going to give Alex guy, we need to kick out, let's get him out of here, Joe
Yeah
Alex you need to stop stuttering girls. We're gonna kick you. It's the wind man
This is a beautiful scene we're seeing right shut up or
The sun's going down over here
Do you have a long cat come catcher under your chair? That's my one Rony's. I mean, it's I'm it
That's that's the smile of I don't pay any bills
Exactly
It's a sunny day
it coming from the person with the cable
I pay for my gas electric
and the gas electric and
what else is there
I pay them all
so wait someone sent you groceries for the week
and you're still going to get McDonald's
is that what you're headed
no I'm going to get a couple of drinks
a whole white cloth
oh okay
hey Alex
do you have cakes
do you have cakes in the store
what
Do you do you have
Do you have cages on your wings out?
Cages on my windows
What does that mean?
No, it's just a question
It's just on my window. It's a brittle. It's a riddle
Windows because I live in California
well
Quite the view pages on your windows. They're not quite cages. They're more like a gates
Oh security gates if you live in a bad neighborhood. Yeah, it's like if you ever seen fucking Friday before everybody's got those bars and on their windows
Yeah
Find a better place. Yeah, because I'll because everywhere in fucking, California
It's all a man's story houses and we're what the mask has to crawl through your window at night
Exactly. So, okay, so Alex from New York, right? I'm from I'm from Pittsburgh
Most people live in townhouses like three-story townhouses like nobody lives in a one-story place
Pretty much everybody lives in a two or three story place.
But in California, especially in Southern California,
most people live in these like one story houses where
if somebody breaks into your window at night, you're fucked.
So yeah, they have these like fucking metal bars.
That's why you don't have the shotgun behind the door.
That's the other alternative, you know?
Well, it's a mandatory you can't have any guns.
That's scary.
That's a mental mindful from the government like hey, buddy. You're gonna need these cages in case someone crawls in the window at night
Leave leave the zoo bro leave the zoo leave the zoo exactly get some fresh air
You got cages on your windows on trackable fuck no
Bro, look here. How about this? I'm a good on stairs. I'm gonna show you exactly what I'm talking about watch
Down I am on the kitchen window look
There is
That's a mental my point because now you're looking at bars every day. Like it's almost like subconsciously
Right the bars are just a subconscious thing. Like you don't even think about it, right? You wake up, you know, this is how they like
The masses I don't know man. What do you think about that is that it did?
It's gonna we know he's pulling a cigarette he's on us
Hi ginger they banned my og account
My babies that's small
those chicken legs don't show those chicken legs my man
I'm so taller than you bitch
Oh my good little Katie
She was your legs fucking on trackable the party happens eyes
Yeah, the cameras boys in your legs actually and trackable when skinny dip in one slide
Be careful
Wait, where's your toy at, baby?
Where's your toy at?
All right, I'll be home in a second.
It's your favorite toy.
Come here.
Those are used to contact?
Or your girlfriends?
Or what, like?
And I'll do my best to get your office.
I was propped out.
someone fucking up psych did you get into a fight with a girl no she was just passing by she's talking about
you're the black lady she's like oh mother fucker
yeah i heard that i'm like what the fuck happened
i went out of my car okay look at her little kitty cat playing it's so cute but look at her
see they're like mini tigers
I know he was like so tough and then he has these little kitties and he loves his kitties
That's what I'm saying, I was just thinking that but I didn't want to say it bro just because whatever
I was like there's Mr. Tough guy, look at him playing with the kitty chat
Love it
Everyone has that side of the game
Closest to Tigers of anything
They're closest to Tigers
They're literally maybe Tigers
They're descendants. Yeah, you're a mini tiger, but I'll stuff up your ass up
You know what I love about past the feet their little pads those shits are crazy
Little patch
You're to a gourd about the damn toy you're too worried about the damn toy ginger
You got a sneaky double in here someone's not getting real quick
It's why you're saying that I'm you know, how did I threaten you bro? How did I threaten you bro?
We're talking about talking to you he's talking to you bro. I don't know me and untrackable never seen this guy in our life, right?
I mean we're talking about cats
What up, you don't catch a wall. I didn't say that name a man. I don't want to call you
Eat a congee nice. You sound like this dude Rocky. Do you know Rocky? Not Rocky the boxer, but Rocky he was like a
Bow and cool
I don't know. He knew a crack rock Chris
No
Who are you talking to though about like whatever
Saki you were saying that he said that I trained him. Yeah, he's not even here at the moment
We'll be back in a minute
What you're saying is true though, man, it's like
Where's the proof, you know what I mean? You were right about that, bro
Yeah, 100% man. I feel that way
I just didn't feel like talking at that time, but it felt like kind of like a little bit
You're like if you came out of your chat, I'm gonna do this and then you've started post
Yeah, that's bullshit while you ban me and then I said shit in discord now because that's fucked up
I was saying oh, you're threatening me
Oh
Get this dude out of here. He's a fucking weirdo every time he comes here. He wants to talk about kids and weird shit
What does he bring to the panel
I
Yes, it's not about his kids and weird shit, man. It's a fucking weird
So I get the defending myself things as well. Yeah, yeah, but I'm slathered me
I don't care because guess what people that matter to me. They don't give us
Brandon you said you're attracted to transgenders
When did I say that in the chat one time? He said you're like transgenders. Oh, I said so I know I said some of them look like chicks
Yeah, they look like a chick. Yeah
Wait, this is branding Q. Yeah
Well, he looks completely different to me and a new name. I had no idea. I thought this was a completely different person
All right
Alice doesn't say the brandy Q go ahead. Let's go ahead. Go ahead up. So you
What's up, bro?
So you're getting a lot of jackets thrown on you by a lot of you know, we've open through it up here man
Just lies people lie up here and people believe it
But y'all are y'all just haven't met him yet that's a thing like y'all just ran into him recently
We already knew this about him for fucking years now that he's a weirdo
Years, the slander started like two a year ago, bro.
Years!
I've only been streaming for two years, bro.
I've only been streaming for two years.
I would love for anybody, anybody to go on BrandonQ's channel right now and look at how
much of a fucking weirdo he is.
You could tell how much, how psychopathic this guy is.
How all it is is video only streaming video games.
This guy is a psycho, dude.
I'm a psycho for streaming video games.
This guy's a fucking psycho.
I'm a psycho for sure you need you need to stop talking to little girls on instagram
and you need to get some fucking professional help tizzy never did never did i'm gonna get some
professional help and you need to stop talking to minors on instagram never did i never did in the
first place i never did in the first place but you know you know you know you're a weirdo
you're a weirdo you spit on a woman bro you're a fucking weirdo and i spit on you too and i spit
on your fucking grandmother you spit on a woman come spit on me i'll spit on you too let's see
you you wouldn't do nothing about it bro get on camp bro get on camp bro come up bro this
Bro, that's that's because that's weak as fuck get on
You and trackable let me see those spaghetti arms you and psyche better kill those are 24 inch pythons. He was just showing look at Ronys
Who's the one on here saying and word and word like bro, how sick in the head do you have to be to use such a disgusting word? Oh
And word and word I'm gonna spit on women spitting on women bro taking advantage of people bro
Hey, just because somebody drew rules doesn't mean it's disgusting. No, that's fucked up, bro
To you
No, in general, bro, like
Do you make the rules? It's not a rule. It's not a rule. There doesn't need to be a rule, bro
There doesn't need to be a rule. It's just common
human decency
Pedophile like here Brandon
Oh
Can you prove that you what you're saying Q or you just fucking lying and throwing jackets on him cuz you don't like the guy
He can't prove it. This is already been gone. There are many times
I don't have ready proof because I don't keep fucking weirdo shit like that on my phone
He had sexual conversations with a girl named rain on Instagram
See look look it out. Look at how mad he's getting look at
You wouldn't begin so mad
Exactly as soon as I start talking about it. He starts getting mad. How do I show my screen psyche?
Yeah, you just had to share it on the stream yard making like I can put it up
Bring the proof to the table and then we'll decide and over this here say she say shit
I'm sick of people just yelling shit like he's a Peter. He's this. He's that without just the dumb words like that means nothing like prove it
Show me something like the fuck
It's like the worst thing you can say about somebody basically and then everyone jumps on the bandwagon, you know
Yeah, he's
To you, but you're not a fucking judge motherfucker, I don't have to prove nothing to you. You're not a judge my man
You better believe it
Bring the proof as well. They know then talk Alex. You were not
Garage my man enough enough is enough 2026 on track. Okay. This is who he's talking about bro
And look who's chat there in a paid member bro. Share my screen
But my screen is not coming up yet. You have to present. I think it's gonna present or yeah, I hit present. Okay, like share screen
Okay
You can add it he doesn't he doesn't know what I got it. I'm doing it right now. I'm doing it right now. You can add it
I got it right now. Okay
Here it is. I want it just went off you to do it again, okay
There, look, dude.
See this?
This is who he's talking about.
That I was talking to some kid or whatever.
Look, there's snowballs.
Notice how the name is green.
look, Nicole and DX, I promise, snowballs, and then you go on and on or whatever, and then Nicole says,
look, besides you're not doing anything wrong.
Who is rain?
And then snowballs, that is rain, bro.
Who is rain, Brandon?
That is rain, bro.
Yeah, look, yes, because I don't want my phone to get damaged and I think I'm in danger.
So now snowballs and rain are the same person?
Nice, do I have to call, do I have to, do I have to get Anita Blunt over here?
Do I have to get Anita Blunt over here?
She's just going to save the same lies as you, bro.
Again, I'm going to get Anita Blunt over here.
Look at that, look at that.
See how the name is green?
That's a 12-year-old, bro.
Where are the paid members that are minors in my stream?
I don't have no 12 year olds that are paying money to be a member and typing in my chat, bro
Okay, so if they're 12 years old, how are they paying money? What credit card do they have? Probably the parents
That's another sad fucking thing right exactly bro. How wrong is now people have exactly exact book. She's saying right here
Yeah, it's just I don't want my
Parents I'm in danger bro. She's saying right here. She don't okay
What what parents take away their kids phone if they're not a little kid, bro
look at that yes because i don't want my parents phone getting my phone getting taken
how would somebody remember if they're not an adult look at that look at that
i'm just saying you could have got baited the did you get baited no that's not me this isn't
me this is another this is the dude right here that dude's face
That's why you got caught right at the end of the fucking conversation with a girl named rain on instagram
You knew that she got her fucking phone taken away from her by her father
You know her that her father was in prison. How did you know all that shit about that little girl's life?
If you weren't talking to her
How did you know so much shit about rain's life if you weren't talking to that 15 year old girl?
She was in Gamble saying it look yeah
Cause I don't want my parents to talk about it
Oh because she was in Gamble
I was in Gamble
Look at that look at that
So Gamble the guy who had passed pedophiles
The guy who had passed pedophiles
That's where you got that information from
It makes a ton of sense right
It makes a ton of fucking sense
What is this? What is this on the screen?
What is this?
You're fucking retard
What's that on the screen bro?
What's that on the screen?
What is that?
Who is that? Is that Gamble or me, bro? Is that Gamble or me?
Who is that right there? Is that Gamble or me?
Brandon Fuentana is a pedophile
This is the dude who started look this is the dude who started look I'm gonna show you something crazy
This is the dude. Oh my mother reina Quintana. It's a fucking pedophile when I've seen the proof
look
Pussy this is the guy started
Yeah, the guy that almost he's bringing receipts you you're not doing this you have to counter with your evidence
So right now Brandon's waiting the cake Alex at this moment highlights suggest
I'm saying this is probably one of those times where you should shut your mouth. I'm just giving you some good
I'm gonna agree with you my man. I'm gonna agree. I'm not being an asshole. I'm not
who's that bro gamble look who's that and then look who's that up there who's
that nobody even sees what the fuck you're talking about who's that you
can't see it look look who's that who's that who is that who's that that's a
ten-year-old that's a ten-year-old bro look and look down there and then look
at this guy with no shirt stupid n-word his name oh my god but no no
So let's say that this is real, what does this prove?
It proves he talks to ten-year-old little boys with no shirt on.
Okay, and you talked to say no, I don't know. I don't prove it
That looks like a little kid
And this is the dude
Look at that, bro. Look that and that's how it gets better, bro. It gets better, bro. Oh my god
It gets better the idea that I have to prove this again
It's crazy because it's like so so because I was around for some history and I've seen things should I have like?
So should I fucking like screen record and clip every single thing that I ever see like
Come on everybody knows you're a PDF. It's not just me that says that
Press one in the chat if you know that Brandon Q has done some questionable shit with miners in the past
That's proof, bro. That's proof.
Press 1 in the chat if you know that Brandon Q has done some questionable things with minors in the past.
Look, look, look, right here.
Everybody knows it's not just me. It's not a fucking conspiracy theory.
Mute him. Look, this is Stephanie. Are you referencing the guy that pursued me first?
Mute him.
Yeah, exactly. Mute him. Mute him. Mute him.
Well, in reality, a friendly friendship should always lead to a romantic interest in his mind while we never dated and never even closed.
as well as he was waiting for my mental house to deteriorate enough to exploit my vulnerability while protecting it.
CHAPTER I found out that he was the person that brags about pushing people to sewer slide
and having nothing better to do than cybersaw people from the comfort of his dad's house.
Unfortunately people who are who are proud waste of oxygen aren't my type and if that makes me
Ex-homegirl that he raised, bro.
Keep having private conversations with 15-year-old girls
on Instagram, you fucking pedo.
I guess you're a pedophile and you're a faggot who had evidence
Who had ever so who's the one with evidence?
Who's the one that had showed evidence that the guy that is accusing me of that started the rumor is actually the one doing that shit, bro
But yet you can't show me that I did something like that show me doing shit like that, bro
Yeah, so I'll go ahead and leave. I'm what I'm gonna do is leave and then he could come back and then let's see
What he has to say, bro, it's letting me on bro, and I'm just maybe mad at you ban me, bro
I like you bro. I mean I'm banned, you know, yeah, I just kicked you off the show for a minute. I like you, bro
Like, okay, you're up and I'll be back. I want him to get back on and see what he says now, bro
Thanks, Brandon
I don't know much about it. It's like I'm running at the bottom of it, but it's like, you know, it's like really like, you know
There's a lot of stuff being said and a lot of like jackets being thrown and all this kind of stuff
I just don't know, you know, so
But at least he brought some proofs and discovery, you know, yeah
The prosecution now has to go over that queue. You got to prove shit, bro
No, can't just fucking say shit and okay. He's this and believe it, you know expect everyone to do it
sucked up
If you open your doors to
Master please
Judicial system
Well, you better bro, don't let me down dick because I don't know this guy from a hole in the wall
But he's coming with some seeds and you
Come on prove me wrong prove me
I'm not here to prove you wrong. I don't have to prove you wrong. Everybody already knows this shit
It's not this is common knowledge that branding Q is a fucking weirdo
Listen, the only difference is is that you're not from the same community
If you would have known branding Q as long as I have you'd be like, yeah, this dude's a fucking weirdo
You'd be like what the fuck psyche? Why do you even have him up here?
If you knew what I knew you'd be saying the same shit, but
Okay, thank you appreciate that
But I know I know for a fact if you knew what I knew
Yeah, Michael Jackson sound
Yeah, you go Ronnie's grab the nuts
I'm just bored and I try to intervene with my dumb shit, but I have no clue. Who knows what I just see the guy putting shit on the screen
Trying to find themselves, but whatever wrong. I want none to do with that. Do you see me there on Bronzeberg's channel, guys?
The other night. Bronzeberg? Yeah, I was on Bronzeberg's channel the other night. Do you want to see a little bit of it?
He said you crashed out.
Yeah, right we can see you can see it. Oh the water on time. Let's see it. Let's watch it
You were naked, right I was a naked
Fucking PDF wants me to sit up here and fucking argue with him like we've already said everything to him
It's all the shit's already been proven like what am I gonna sit up here and argue with him for so when he comes up here
I just leave I don't have to argue with this dude
Everybody fucking knows this dude's a weirdo, right? He looks young. How old is he?
He's like 30 fucking he's like 33 34
And somebody said that he's a weirdo pdf and he's saying no, I'm not the same shit like everyone else kind of thing
He has a sexual and explicit conversations with 15 year olds on
Okay, what you call it?
And what is this guy? What is this guy gamble coming to a pedophile a hundred percent if you if you would consider somebody who has
sexual and
personal conversations with a 15 year old
On Instagram
Then yes, he is
Okay, and he was older
He ever fucked an underage woman not saying that but he's definitely had
Communications with more than one underage woman
Do you have communications though? That's why my judge sheet comes in like you have those communications
You can produce them and show them to us like you can't go to the cops and say listen this guy does this
I know he'd been texting like you have to show them
The text and then they'll be like all right
You can believe me or not
That's fine doesn't work that way. I don't I don't have enough space on my phone to keep dirt on every fucking pdf in this community
I would need a phone with 250 gigabytes
So why is he throwing gamble under the bus? Is that his like a scapegoat?
Oh, so that's
No, he came on that moment right there just a fucking talk, you know
He always comes like just to get you know a little bit of attention and then he'll rage quit and leave
I don't hear what the point is trying to describe a gamble because gambler's the one exposing him
He's the one hunting his ass
The gamble literally hunts good files and was trolling him for months
But this is a crazy thing about tonight
Then Gamble left YouTube and when he just like gave up YouTube he was like sick of streaming
So he gave up YouTube and now Brandon thinks that he took some sort of W against him
No, that means nothing
What a fuck you got a suit of counts
Have to be yelling he can be
What are you talking about, Frankie?
The neighbors are gonna hear you screaming again.
You need a wellness check, bro?
You need a wellness check?
Frankie, you're yelling again.
What are you yelling about?
Don't you think you're doing this stream right now?
You're gonna lose your voice tomorrow.
What?
Calm down.
So you just came over here to call Beto a bitch?
I can't even hear what you're saying the way you're yelling.
You just, nobody can hear you, bro.
So I'll get to that broke mic you have he's broken bro. He is we all know it is
That's a George Floyd. Where's George Floyd that guy look that guy's pretty hot. Where's George Floyd?
He's talking about where's George Floyd and so you're saying George Floyd
Because you want any races funny. He thinks he's funny about saying some racist shit
This is this is his way of trying to act like he went on my stream and he tried to trigger me with some bullshit
Oh my god, he's so good
Bro, can you not do that fucking weird shit, bro?
Nobody wanna see a little skinny ass, bro
Broz, bro, what are we gonna do against this
Why is this crack hand twerking on my stream, bro?
What the fuck is he doing?
Stop shaking your ass on my stream, weirdo
You don't wanna see this
Fuckin' dickhead
He's broken.
Is this dude serious?
Like, this is a way of trying to troll me.
Why are you playing this, dickhead?
What the fuck?
Stop grabbing your dick on my fucking street, bro.
It's not cool.
Oh, my god.
He did the Michael Jackson.
He did the Michael Jackson nice.
This is wild, bro.
This is some real nigger shit.
What the fuck is going on?
Why are you talking about George Floyd though?
Why is he bringing up George Floyd?
What does George Floyd have to do with anything?
He really thinks he's going to be able to get to me.
This is, this is like his lore, so you can say people fell into his trap, whatever the fuck that means.
Hey, eat my asshole.
How many people you blocked out your chat today you tried to
Alexander don't fuck with you no more
I've seen I know she don't
People are not psyche that psyche verse bullshit
Did you have a boyfriend that you was talking about
Took him on an AI day to some restaurant. You can't
Why I heard Alexander Alexander McQueen's your sugar daddy
I thought it was called a pee-pee
He said you see how he said I'm gonna let him expose himself, bro
He just sit up there and say the n-word like you doing nothing. He's sort of racist told me
Bro, I heard what you said, bro. I'm not stupid. I wasn't born yesterday psyche
He's giving us the recipe
How does he have like all this professional setting, but his audio is like
Oh, you're dumb dirty. You've got a white tongue dirty ass nails and shit
Bro, he made a whole song he had to make a whole song dedicated to his
Reminds me of like
Like he doesn't look as nasty as fuck fuck you got issues
I don't care
Ronys, you got that Michael Jackson crap the cock shit down
You got it down my man
I just want to laugh how dumb that looks
He really did that shit bro
That's insane by the way that you got the fuck above it like holy shit, that's so crazy
Love it
Stop fucking ruining Ronys
Oh
Only Michael Jackson in one of the videos they turned you besides Manson I could have sworn there was
A roomies Jackson somewhere
Um, yeah, they got TripKick has turned me into like, you know, I'm in like actually 15 movies now on TripKick
Okay, I think this is Michael Jackson video. Let me see. Let me see
Yeah, and yeah, and everyone we're having a fun night tonight. This is just like a
This is like a free-for-all sakey free-for-all, but let me see. Let me see. Where's Michael Jackson shit. Let me see
Oh, here it is. I'm gonna see it. I was gonna see it
I'm waiting buddy. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I asked for it. He bit your ass. I want to see it. Here you go
I'm gonna right here. Okay. Sure. Okay, there we go
There it is folks buckle up
You suck you fucking suck bitch
The fire's in their eyes, and their words are really clear
So feed it, just feed it
You better do, you better do if you can't
Yo, would be afro, that's too much, man, man
You wanna be, you just better do if you can't
So feed it, but you wanna be
Yeah!
Yeah, person sending people to my house, the last thing I'm ever gonna say to you again,
It didn't work. It didn't work, and now it's over.
Please, there's no link because I'm not on StreamYard or anything,
but you can talk from the chat. And BlackRG, so let me see.
Is he a good guy?
Not particularly. The first time I came across BlackRG,
he was doxing Vita, did a whole episode.
Well, now I don't even care that you did that,
but it did lead into him telling that he had a spy.
Okay, that's good. He had a spy in my discord the whole time,
and you're okay, fine. You're not a good guy then.
Yeah, he's just if he wants to be everyone's friend, you know, until he like fucking betrays them and stabs in the back
There I don't know. I don't know for your particularly fair
Vita stuff or spy discord imagine that they go spy. Oh, thank you
neutral on black are you neutral on him? I had no I have absolutely no feeling
Yeah, so I would say the the word the most evil person. I would say it's Vita. She is the fakest person absolutely the fakest person
biggest
I don't know, she's just going to fake a new name, fake friend, buddy troll, liar.
She lets people be abused, lets her friends be abused.
She also, she will not go live without having a bunch of people lined up to defend her,
right?
She'll even, and I know about this for a fact, who she mails and says, oh come on and
Yeah, it's funny. There's long of it. I know you know, it's funny about be that she said I just started streaming
I just started streaming. Oh, you did it really? Oh, you just started really even around for years and years and years
Thank you for a reason I'm sure she did
I'm not gonna mention anything about the situation ever again, you know, so fake
So fake
It was just like if BAKE had a look in the dictionary under BAKE, her picture is there.
Everything.
And she doesn't look anything like, even her bad pictures are flattering her, okay?
I'll put it that way.
I wonder if I would fuck Bita.
I think about that sometimes.
Like what?
Awful.
Baby drunk.
Yeah, real life.
You have to see her real life.
I can't I can't imagine I'm because so many pictures
Another one that came in
Yeah, yeah, was that
Sam Hill is Fred hunts Fred. Yeah, I know
CX. Yeah, like the biggest biggest way to say you're not a pedophile is to like go be a pedophile hunter
And they'd be the biggest that's crazy
No, but it makes sense that psychology 101 exactly it but Jesus, but we still don't know
I mean we can think these are all just theories at the moment because
I don't most of the time real life was him as big in patriot when she was kind of passed out
Is he took a shirt off and stuff? It's kind of all I saw it was pretty inappropriate, but
At the same time, I don't think she's pretty man. I mean she has a nice body. I guess a little kind, you know
But her face, I don't know who is being patient or beta.
No, a vegan patriot.
OK, that's that.
No, he does cute.
I like I think, you know, from the image of a beta, she's cute.
She's hot.
That's how your marriage is a supermodel.
I love her.
She's so cute.
Jesus.
Yeah, she's beautiful, man. That's on your mayor. She's beautiful.
Yeah, I was on the mayor's. Yes, I was on the mayor's beautiful page is beautiful.
Summer's beautiful. Christine is beautiful. What? Um, I mean, come on. I got to throw her in there,
Ronnie. Sorry. I just I just let me get pretend you were out of the room and then hear it.
All right. Christine is beautiful. Kate, the turtle, the Tuga,
Well, she doesn't like you now either the Tuga. No, she doesn't need to destroy me tonight
But what for what she was up here like a month ago with us like yay now. It's back to kill
This is a bipolar panel and a half well, you don't know
Well fuck is that?
No, it's not take yes, it is he doesn't have those big boobs and she's not pregnant and those arms
Those are Joe Shipley arms, bro. I
Swear I all I said was I put it through the eyes. I just make it a cartoon image
So it's not like the real image, but yeah, that's beta
No, you know beat is you got the video beta bro in the mirror putting the cake on her tits
That's beta. That's the closest we got to beta and when she changed her underwear and that but that was like a ground view
You know the angles can be mistaken like you can't really tell what she looks like the closest we got
Oh, no, fuck that. She I saw a video of her live like you right now back in the day on her couch
beta
So yeah, I don't know what you look like actually I forgot what I saw that is that from you or her
Yeah back like a year or two ago before all this shit
There's a video far on a couch talking just like you are right now same thing bro
But like an hour
Everything ever since the picture of Christine is a little pleasure. Look at my Christine chicken lady that hates you to death
No psyche
Fuck that psyche, she's hurt man.
She'll get over it. Wow. I mean wow. Oh, okay. Oh
Everyone's eyes so big who's fuckable. I don't know. I'm fuckable
But I only have Q comes over here. You can fuck me. He wants to fuck me
He was pissed. He was pissed. He didn't like that little interaction
The guy came up here and throw that shit up there and then me like getting in between like prove a Q
So that fucked with him a little my back. You I'm just
I think you might be a gay man
No, he could be right as well. Like even though the guy showed all that shit that wasn't so what so gamble and there was a kid in the corner
I don't get it. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know
That's why I said change the subject when I came in the chat and I saw that guy
I hope you're talking about that and he like took a person. He's like, what do you mean change the subject in the front of
Myself, bro, just change the subject. Here's the Kate the turtle
She posted this today to
My tuga is she still a Barry? I think so
What did I say?
Read it out loud
Well, no the cage show mentioned you in a post while you really are sick
You just let that man speak
Disparaging on an innocent kid at cult of psyche. I will make it my goal to destroy you
All right. So in a court of law, first of all, who was disparaging an innocent kid?
Who was the man?
Brennan Hughes said, Kate's kid was a midget or something like that.
And I said, don't talk about kids.
Oh, that's fine.
That was it.
I mean, at the end of the world, it's just a joke, right?
Right.
That's not the worst thing I've heard out here.
I mean, that doesn't constitute destroying psyche, Kate.
It's not like he controls what comes out of the guy's mouth, and I said he said it
I said don't talk about kids on it too right after that
And you probably didn't kick him right away, and that's what Kate comes in like oh you let this guy up there
Disparaging what a crazy word though, right?
Just say you let some guy talk shit about my kid
Trying to get old fancy on us. By the way, Kate
Sure the other night talking my family talking about how much money she's in me week
Talking about I'm a trust on baby Charlie. I've got all this all this kind of bullshit, right? It's like and it's like
She doesn't know anything about it
No, no reason to speak about it, but speaking of my family then say I'm talking about her kids and stuff a little bit hypocritical
I think my opinion but
You know bears fair all here in in the loving 40 diamonds in the war. Yeah, the world of roses remember that lovely marriage
That's a good movie
It's awesome
How have you been I miss you? I miss you my bro. You're my bro. You know you're my bro. I miss you so I've been good man
I've been good
Hopping around
you know what you go to any chat you want I don't care if you're in my chat or
somebody else's chat but I just want to know you're my friends so and like 100%
for you number one dick
am I number one my man you know it's like an anonymous donor sent me a week of
groceries today for my air fryer and they sent me a white claw you heard
I heard who the how was that angel god bless them
a week of grocery and she's an angel I'll say she's an angel
It's amazing you know God blesses you bro. I
You got to think about this when you're down and out remember back
You know how many times you were just laying like like it's over. No one likes me
Oh 70 watching a week of groceries a lot of people love you
Don't let the ten retards. I hate you. You know cut out the hundred people that actually love you
And I want to show one more time. I want to show one more time the
The commercial plus like the interview with Alexander mayors you can comment during Alex too like
We'll be up here while it's playing, but this is like she came on
She's the only person to talk to me during the brand brand acute scandal and actually tell me stuff about him and stuff
So this is what happened. I'm in plans for from the beginning. Okay
Go ahead comment comment on it. This is this is
something really cool that she did for me and here you go here you go I got it
so here's the there's the video here you go guys look a love folks enjoy you got
it I got it okay full screen welcome to Nicole welcome to the cold guys here we
Living in California, have a criminal history under the age of 30, familiar with Santa Muerte,
into live streaming, enjoy distributing illegal substances.
If so, you might be.
This is my favorite thing on earth.
This girl is funny.
Hi.
No, you're not.
Good.
How are you tonight?
Oh, okay.
In the clip.
Oh my God.
Tell me she's good.
It's a big topic right now.
So let me just keep it real with me.
Are you just entertaining the brand in Q thing because you feel like being defiant?
or because you genuinely feel this is good he's addressing you about the
branding okay I don't I I don't know him like he like I basically I might have
talked to him on a panel once like I like maybe last year but he's just he
comes and he just like I don't I've never seen this picture I don't know what
he looks like or anything he's coming type to my chat a few times and so we
type in my chat a few times today and I had like people that are kind of like
You know, like, you know, fifth stage in a cake and a bunch of other people, including Tony, who sends me the concrete and stuff like that, started going nuts on me and telling me what to do.
He even sent me it on the disability site. He's like, we tell you how to run your show. You don't run your show. We tell you how to do it.
And so that's the defiance coming out, like, of me, because I was like...
So one of your stalkers is trying to push you into not having BrandingQ, so that's the reason that you're having, okay, I see.
And this is not the first time.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, well...
Oh my god, he's a genius.
So you don't know anything about how confused
are you just choosing not to look?
Well, here's what I heard a couple things.
I heard that he was on the monkey app one time,
and the monkey app is like random people will come up.
As far as I know, about the monkey app, it's 18 or over app.
But I guess sometimes people are not 18 on that.
And so somebody, I guess, 16 or something might have come up.
And so that's one story I heard.
And then I heard that he had some run-ins with the law.
like he robbed an old lady's house or like and then um if he was arrested and stuff like that and so
it's funny how corruption is real it's in the middle just so quiet
as I can people be I just I don't know the answer to these questions but I was like can
people be rehabilitated can they change their ways can they have regrets
Can they change or do the deserts be just ostracized?
I don't know all the stories.
Has anyone who you've trusted within these communities
talked to you about this about his history?
Known for a long time?
No, like, no.
And I would like I would have appreciated, like, you know,
someone reaching out on Discord kind of more in a private thing
and like letting me know, like, this is this.
Because the only person who wrote me on Discord was Tony.
And so with these video clips,
that I just going to make heads or tails up really and.
Plus, like trying to say, oh, well, you know, and then he sent me these. Oh, and then all of a sudden the chats saying I'm predator protector
I'm like, I'm oh, I'm gonna say we did a speculating and he's donating money to me or something
I've never received a dime from this person. I don't know what he looks like. I've seen him in chat
Do you haven't received any money from Brandon Q? No, I swear to God. Well, we have clarification on that
That's all I was grinding to you if you don't want me asking
He's um a young man who's in these communities who I think has attempted to loosely model
himself over someone who I actually think very or like Joe Blum off my man but he's the opposite
of gamble so I am going to um let you know a few things about Brandon Q now
Brandon Q over the years, I tried to give him a chance and he has very low impulse control. He
issues threats very readily. He does not have any sort of respect for authority. He is very
predatorial when it comes to vulnerable women. Now, you already know, Psyche, I do not think well
However, something did happen to her in conjunction with Brandon Q that regardless of how much
disdain I may have for her, what happened wasn't right.
He invited her over, streaming sort of thing.
This was at a point in her life where she really didn't have many options as far as
where to stay.
He said that she could stay over at his place.
And when she was trying to sleep, and this was strained, and thank God it was, he was very physically aggressive with her.
It looked like if the camera had not had been on it it probably would have turned into an essay sort of
Situation that in my mind should be enough
But I just did a live stream
Questioning people who are questioning you
If it was come on you're gonna beat the girl up on live stream in his chat and on his panel
Because if you don't have an issue with these other people some of the some of the people in your chat right now
Don't have an issue and I'm not gonna name who's on my list, you know, I'm forever making lists
But they're hypocrites if they're not questioning these other people in conjunction
with Brandon Q. Now, ideally, I would like all these people to no longer be on social media,
but is that going to happen now? But what I will say on your behalf, Psyche, is, look,
if you're going to question Psyche, then...
Well, other way, whatever it were.
Yeah, yeah, we got to choose on this panel too, because that's just how it is.
And really, these entire communities are entrenched with verifiable, legally documented, often charged and convicted.
Predators. Wait, is that the video of Q and vegan in the corner?
But one thing I will say to you and I'm not chastising you or maybe I am in my own way, but I'm just gonna say it
Stop trying to gain acceptance from losers, please.
Gotcha.
I mean, like every other choice of the people was like...
For a while, you were saying that two people who have been atrocious to you are like prom, king, and queen?
No.
Well, I was making an analogy saying that it's too, that was too far of a break.
Thank you Matt, looking for acceptance, you beautiful girl.
Have you not seen him telling you all your bitches to shut the fuck up?
Everything? Is that looking for acceptance?
They're very like, you know, kind of like popular.
Did you really go to, okay, I have to, I just ask you one more question.
Now I'm going to go.
Okay.
I think that you really might be an extraterrestrial who learned all about humanity from watching
and who just every once in a while visits Earth, but you don't quite understand the Earth culture
yet.
Is that what it's got to be?
I do feel like an alien. I'm in Aquarius Moon, which is like the alien's sign.
I'm just gonna, I'm from now on, I'm just gonna say you're an alien.
I agree, I'm saying he could be an alien.
She's on something with that shit.
Ha ha ha, this is not your average puppy.
You know people are gonna be like, oh Alex made that live she know I did go through your codex
When are you gonna fix the codex? And why why do I have?
Seven or eight entries and then people who are always on your panel have zero entries because it scrapes like it
Sometimes I like a rescreen. You got it. You got a fix
There's so much Alexander McQueen up there
Yeah, you got incorporated a little more like that
When you type Alex I pop up in the codex baby
My uses resets and so you thought at least for the for the
Menu or list of people there needs to be an alphabet string
Where people if you just want to look at the C's or you want to look at the K's or you want to look look at the D's
Because right now even searching
For example, J-Dog, he's a frequent guest on your show. He should be listed as a guest,
not just mentioned. But you have to put in J-Space-D-O-G instead of his J-D-O-G-G, his YouTube
name. So, I mean, I guess a lot of people would think to do that, but some people wouldn't. So,
it's not complete. So, I bitched about your codex in the live.
I bitched about it.
Well, tell them to check out, because actually, it's like 34.
If you want to be eight, you're just going to be the leader of the Bad Boys Club.
Is that going to be what it is?
Well, I don't want to be, but here's what.
Here's the thing.
You want to be.
I mean, I think, especially with your new toy cube, do you have a problem with that?
Well, I don't know.
Well, I don't know, he sends big signals and stuff, but uh...
Oh, you're having a blast. I've been watching.
He's fine. He's cute, and then he kisses me off, and then it's like, but um...
I think that, um, okay, my dad was a big true crime person, and so I'm really...
To rub him broken silence, he couldn't hold it in. You heard him laugh?
If someone has the allegations or if they've done something, I would like to talk to them
and like get to the bottom of their psychology about it. I'm like, I'm not, I'm not, like, I'm...
Not in support of their actions anyway but I do think that some people like have made terrible
mistakes and they they go to regret it and I think I do believe and that is redemption.
You just want to create an army of hot Latino guys who terrorize women on occasion that become
your boy toys so you can be the king of the bad boys club.
Are you getting Alex all into this?
I'm a fan of Hugh Hefner. I always have been.
I'm talking about Alex McQueen. That's you Alexandra.
I'm sorry, Alex McQueen I'm talking about.
Oh, oh, okay. Well, Alex McQueen and I, when I really think about it, we're not too different.
I guess that's why we're both Alex's.
But I'm gonna get going. I just wanted to find out your thoughts and everything on it.
Because you're the talk of the town. Talk about YouTube streets.
And I really appreciate it, um, you talking to me because it's like,
because nobody would, nobody like came up on the panel to like talk to me about it.
Like I would like that, but it's like kind of like being yelled at at the chat.
I just kind of like was like, you're not going to tell me what to do.
Chat, like I was like, chat doesn't always win.
I win today, but you know, it's like, sometimes it's like, sometimes some fights
are not worth, well, just be careful.
I don't want any of the bad boys club members to do anything bad to you.
So thank you.
Uh, yeah.
Well, she's so protective over you. I love it
The bad boy members club. I want to see her list of that club
Jesus we hurt
Cheers, so happy like I reconciled like I'm so happy like you know, I could imagine bro
You really you really like that you were heartbroken by that shit. I'm so happy for you as well. You reconcile that
Yeah, oh my lord. I was here but old nor be just coming around. Don't worry. She's next. Yeah, be it was
Hey, be it was like, how would you like it if your father was in that picture a cartoon with the
Cuz Q had a picture up of like
Well, it looks like me I thought but it's I guess it was Sam and I was like and somebody but I didn't know
I I don't know every like little picture people put up what it means and like all the
I get I get the brunch of it though, right?
Watch thing in the stream yard chat. Hey, what's a Brandon's?
masses tits Brandon's Brandon's massive tits, okay?
He's coming out
I don't know someone says watch out. Check the YouTube link in stream your chat. I guess someone's ready to come up
Yeah
Drop down and watch the chat. Oh, you're fine. You're fine. You're fine
I can get mods in there. I'm gonna go for a minute walk walk to the liquor store
I know you have a couple more cigars. I have a friend coming
I wrote
We're gonna do some IRL guys. This is my role. I'll walk down the street. I'll be right over. What's the best?
Alex you stay with me. You gotta keep the camera steady in front of you showing I
Will I will you know how I do when I go like the Dunkin Donuts. You see how it's like steady and I'm sure
It's not like oh
Because the IRL is awesome. I'll be the same again. He talks to the chat for a minute. I'll be right back
My little Chatteronies have no idea who's in here all them off
We just watched a good show Alexander man's
But to get some IRL from Roni's
Here we go
Hit the subscribe button guys and the fucking like man, it's free. It's courtesy
Neighbors will buy us a little staircase well, it's so clear and beautiful
Nice little area walking around man, that's an understatement my man. Don't rub it in
It will come back back
There Alex
Yes, sir. Hi captain. Hey, here we go. Why don't you roll?
Pompiers up there. It's gonna be an Hollywood in the
What is a nice area nice little houses, California, look at that
California, no doubt about it
California, no doubt about it, in the city, my dream was to go to UCLA, bro, as a little
kid, UCLA.
I used to.
UCLA?
So my brother, I think my brother went to UCLA, my dad went to USC, I graduated my older
brother went to UCLA.
and, uh, he's really smart, like, uh, I could never get into UCLA, I went to a, I went to college, I was like, uh,
easy college to get into and I failed out of it, my little brother, my little brother went there, he passed, he passed, he went, he graduated, but, you know.
There were two, but you said you had four, that was only two.
So, one, you sealed that.
I have one younger brother, one younger sister, and then I have, I have three older brothers and one older sister, and so that's seven kids.
the
So they have is either channel. I'll still be on one of the other
Yeah, you're not alone by the way Ronis this week fucking money for 20 got demonetized
That I trippy cat got the monetize. I saw like four people
It's a monetize. Yeah, the AI bots. So I
You know what it is. They don't want to repeat it in this because YouTube
Revenue right from their sponsors. Yeah, so yeah, they don't like
Because I did some series like and so they were like maybe repetitive because there was a series and they're like, okay
Well that you know you made it with AI or whatever and so I can reply when all my strikes are gone
And that will be very soon like at least maybe a couple months
It's like it's not like it's like it's like whenever the strikes are
Expired and so it's probably a couple months, but I'll be able to reply
I'm gonna put all my AI content onto like psychies AI channel or whatever all my videos all my
All the stories
TOS you gotta control the n-word and you gotta control anything
You know with the that starts with J and it and ranks with ooze
Kind of talk like all that shit YouTube doesn't like it because they would do this one ad revenue, right? So no
Person of McDonald's or company is gonna want you to represent them when the end was fine, right?
I bet none of my none of my none of my videos. I don't I don't monetize any of my videos specifically
All I had was the membership going
And so it shouldn't have had anything to do.
I wasn't trying to monetize any videos,
but there are shorts, I guess, with the,
and I don't know why they do it,
or why the poor reason or whatever.
When somebody reported that and we're in all that bullshit,
so they just demonetized.
And, but you do actually do make content
that like helps and teaches shit.
The color reading, like, you know, that's good.
They like that.
I think my god was good, but they're repetitive of just panels people talking shit
They don't like and especially when it gets all racist and shit. That's when the monetization comes in the picture
Like it's just so
It's just like they turned it they turned it off and I said I could turn it back on
When I said I could fix the channel and stuff in a few months
I can I can like delete videos and stuff and obviously this channel is gonna be all like the live streams
The whole the psyche will be like some other stuff and then I'll have a third channel for the AI stuff that I do
It's not just AI. It's like me using
People one channel for the nightmares, you know for the bullshit
So that gets fucked or whatever, but have your main channel monetized
Hold the psyche that one needs to be flown and protected
The sort of nightmares
I like the Cash App, if you will get a reading or a song request from Cash App, because that's instantly, you know, I get the money, but it's like, because on YouTube, like, YouTube was holding my paycheck for this month, you know, so it's like a couple hundred bucks.
Once you get like really back in the flow of things, remember when you were making like a grand a month, like you said you did, and I remember that month.
That was a good month.
That's how it goes, that's how it goes.
It goes to 90% of that.
Yeah, because it goes you don't need like
That was too fucking the not that wasn't cash out, right? That was like the about through the YouTube. Hey, there's squirrel this squirrel
This is a little bit squirrel
This is a squirrel. There was a squirrel by the way
Goat was wanting me about being Tony the conductor and he was kept playing the stupid train thing
That's a lie. You know, we should go by the house. That's him doing it. He doesn't live next to a train. I
don't know
Yeah, that's like the doffin noise on your computer. No, I was with him the other night
And I swear to God it's like I was with him on no
I forgot what panel is either monies or less is like a night or two ago
And I was like you Tony fuck and he was laughing and I played the fucking play them train for me
And he did it to chew and he kept doing it over and over for like 10 minutes straight laughing like
No, but it doesn't keep passing by fucking to chewing for 10 minutes straight
Okay, he was doing it and he knew he was we like broke that barrier
He let me know like he's was calling us with that shit whether he's told
But he's a
You there trackable
Yes, I hear you. Okay. Good. I said put the camera forward and study and it's just your big noggin your big noggin and unsteady
But I know you don't want to show them a neighborhood because some cycle
You know, I can track you down to all I gotta do is find that McDonald's and back walk your little five-minute walk
Hello, that's if you look at your shadow. Look at your shadow. That's so funny
the
I
Fucked with you. I'm not trying to
Yeah, I'll be right back. I'm gonna go get I'm gonna get some fries or something. I'll be right back
branchy fries
Hey, what's up, bro? It's your new again
Yeah, hey, these are where the beautiful moments are made that's when it happens the magic
But you're a dick talking about you know, I
Mean anyway, you've been bro
I've been doing very where you've been where have you been is a better question
Not how, where? I haven't seen you around.
I've been basking in the sun, brother.
Are you tan? Did you get a nice tan? Do you have tan lines on your fucking tits?
I knew that was gonna hit me.
Bro, I know how to deliver for the stick missiles. I'm like, he's like...
Boom, let's go. Let's go. You have 10 lines on them on that hairy cheek of yours. Oh
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I wore high socks while I mowed the lawn. Oh
My god, what a dork you like the guy from fucking a police academy
That falls asleep on the beach and they put dork on him and on his chest with son
So then when he wakes up, it says
dork
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
He's got dork fucking tan land on his chest. What's up, dork?
You're great
Hey, I
Haven't seen I'm gonna do you guys a freebie. I dorked out one time in Puerto Rico
I fell asleep with sunglasses on my man when I took them off
You can only imagine
the whole steakhouse was having fun that night at dinner like ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Back in my younger days
We left the college campus at night and we were gonna go towards the beach and
You know, we saw a cover band play
and a
Couple of us were like, hey, we're gonna watch the sunrise
But you know, we had been at school all day and then we drove
Several hours and then we get to the beach
And, you know, just watching the night time.
Ronys, Ronys is done.
And then the sun comes up.
And we're like, dad, that's beautiful, that's amazing.
We just watched the sun, you know, rise up over the ocean.
And then we felt like...
Like Dave Fox, you watch the sunset together with a bunch of guys,
you're telling me? Where does the darkness come in?
No, but but then we watched the Sun rise a watching the Sun said it's
Watching the Sun
That's a you know, that's a couple thing
We we we were sitting there asleep getting baked by that early morning Sun for like three hours
On one side you could watch it the Sun rise for your boys you can
And then there was another time
of all was in south korea
and then you look like a door when you took it off was there a tan lines
of the door, there was no tan when you get baked on one side of the
You you get you get tan when you spend an hour and then chill and then spend an hour and then chill
You mean you get 15 minutes of vitamin D a day after that you're cooking yourself like bacon on a pan
When you lay on a beach for an hour
You're just not as cooking you like bacon
Oh, no fucking 90 at 40 because you're just some tan guy like bro stay the son is not our friend
I mean we needed I get it living on that shit, but you have to know what I'm gonna do that
It'll kill you bro
And honestly think about it if you stay in the Sun forever, you're gonna blister that thing will kill you
Hey, I think we worked like this on and we needed things to give a fuck about us
I should have killed us in the second and and this is part two like
Somebody
I went to the
Fucking blisters in your eyes. I
was in South Korea and
I got the chance to go to the ocean
And there was this dude. He I think it was from like Iowa or something like that
Nick of time you're a moron because he's apple pies all the time
Apple he's fruit my man
And so
The this dude had never been
Strawberry pie strawberries of fruit nick of time
He had never been outside of shirt off
Oh
Oh my god
And we went down to the ocean
And it's freezing cold like the ocean was freezing cold, but you know I went and did my swimming thing and I
He wouldn't get past the thing.
Apple pie, fruit, burning joint, shut the fuck up.
Banana milkshake, banana.
Don't ever say fruit again.
This guy's a fruit attrition.
Oh, he eats the fruit.
I think the coffee's like fucking vanilla's coffee.
Isn't that vanilla fruit?
You know?
It's fruit and everything.
Way to enjoy a story Alex
Sorry, man, but they're attacking sighting in the chat bro. They doesn't eat fruit and they have no clue what they're talking about
Sorry, I'm interrupting go
They are they attacking Roni about room
Yes, so
Remember McDonnell by packages attacks warning hot content. Yes
I don't know that dick you're in Russia
Oh
I'm gonna meet up
He doesn't believe me now
Yeah, so then there was this moment where it was like
And
The wind is overpowering you and then they call us I
I felt
Yeah, I got burned
I
That's fine with me
This this dude from Iowa
Had never seen the Sun before
And I show look like he can help me through the phone the TV and
And then and then the next day
Like we got to go to work
His entire back was blisters
And look what kind of drink is that Ronis? Is that a strawberry something and and everybody knew it and
Somebody decided to say hello with a big old back slap
And and you could see that
They slapped you on the back of your head not not me old boy from Iowa
well
And what happened how do you react to that backslap?
You you could see the blistered juice coming through his uniform
I'm gonna lie I was in pain because I was sunburned
but he was in pain because he's never been sunburned before
it's like the fourth time I could walk to the store today
yeah
that donor muster
Jesus
it's good to take a walk
I can only get one
maybe I don't even think I've gotten more than two out of
four times
when's the last time you took a walk out
I can't even remember actually yeah, so shut your fucking mouth
There you go
So continues to the story dick it was just getting good
Oh, that was the end of the story. Oh, I finished the story you just didn't listen I
Had no clue what you said the whole time now one word
Cuz it's all about you
Come on, I don't you want to laugh let it out let it out
Well, I'll laugh when you say something funny. How about that?
Hmm interesting how do you make time fly?
Throw a clock out the window
Yeah
Just click the button and listen to Alex. That's how you make time fly
I like on track, when he says I need to quit my batteries at 5%.
He's like Drupi, the cartoon. They're calling you Drupi D.
You remember that cartoon? It was a dog with long ears.
I think he sounds like fucking Eeyore from Winnie the Pooh.
Uh, don't worry about me. Nobody ever does.
Haha, that's untrackable. He's Eeyore.
He's down in Beverly Hills and life, and he just walks throughout the whole show like oh, I don't pay my garage cuz I'm fucking your
That's it, bro
you remember the story of Snow Wife in the Seven Dwarves
I do
Hey, I'm Alex and I'm the Kokey Dwarf
Oh, wow, that was great
I'm Alex and I'm the Kokey Dwarf, the Coke, the Coke, that's funny
Yeah, because not only you
but you're always stoned, motherfucker
I'm always stone
Wow, you have to stay stone this day and age. I mean, come on. You ever seen what reality looks like my boy
You want to tackle that shit sober? Oh, okay
Life is boring when you're sober in my eyes. It's like so boring like oh fuck this sucks like
There's some
But you know that's fucked up because low enforcement you have to be sober
No, no, that's not that mine
We should we should both go trans and we should both
We should both praise Islam
So that way we could wear hijabs
and the moment we take off and
And and like profess our loves to each other in public
Then we'll really get stoned. You know what I'm saying?
No, did you just say become a tranny and Iranian get he jobs for them off and play with our dicks like I don't know what the fuck you just had to me.
I don't think he said that.
No, that's that's how I took it anyway so somebody interpret what the fuck he just said bro.
I mean, if you if you really want to get stoned
You got to do some crazy shit, bro. I
Got to be coming on a heat job. I ranians get stoned take it up. I
Don't know even to change the subject. I'm gonna pull a branding cue on you. Let's change the subject my man
Whoo, I know it was it was uncomfortable to tell in that joke
Yeah, especially what was happening now, bro with the Iran shit
I mean, I'm upset with high gas prices
Yeah, that's that's fine. You said for a dollar
More, you know, it's happening out there in my mind World War three is on the break
I have been the most
Advocate for you know, let's stop killing each other. I've been as much as I can about that, but I know what's gonna happen
And you know if you participate
Ready for what's coming up man, cuz they're gonna attack again a third aircraft carrier just got there
That never happened ever
That's three air airports. They surrounded the country, but you know neck our car is basically an airfield
Like we don't need an airfield. We'll bring the airfield to you like we have our own airports floating airports in the sea
at the end of the day
It's not gonna go good, but what's about that? I
Don't like to see I would I would love to see world peace
but um
Come on shit going on for that problem. I think well peace is not the window. I think that ship has sailed are you
What the old reality you win world peace, bro? We're at the brink of fucking war. This is war war war everywhere
Russia Ukraine the United States Iran China was Taiwan buddy world peace. That's not the window for now
The only thing I'm in charge of is buying my own fucking shoes and
We move on from there
So wait, we're just watching this shit
I've watched my parents watch war on TV and they were not happy with it
It was like I'm not happy with it, but you know what?
What the hell are those things like? They're so cigars, but not like the Cuban cigars. They're like many ones
sweet
They're not sweet because they're not yeah, I'm a sweet flavor that is after your normal cigars because of California, but they're they are
You imagine that's your dick you I'm just like rolling it around
Imagine that I'm sorry. Yeah
Okay, let me sorry your panel. I need something to open a wine bar. I'm terrible. Sorry. He should be sorry
It's okay
I mean if it wasn't for the three of us then who would either of us have to talk to right now
this is so gay and I'm so proud and I use that word so liberally I am so proud
We're a guest. We have a guest coming on.
Let's welcome our guest, The Good Truth.
Hello.
Hello?
How y'all doing?
Who is this?
Welcome, bro.
I'm Psyche's friend.
You're Psyche's friend? Okay.
The goddamn knickers are discovered here!
What the fuck?
Okay, I'm gonna restart the stream.
I'll be right back, guys.
Thank you so much.